<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tasty Dishes</string>

    <!-- Admob AD ON or OFF -->
    <string name="show_admob_ad">ON</string>

    <!-- Device ID  setTestDeviceIds (search on logcat for device id) -->
    <string name="device_id">ABCD</string>

    <!-- Admob APP ID HERE -->
    <string name="admob_APP_ID">ca-app-pub-4931336900110358~8433657311</string>
    <!-- Admob Ad Unit IDS Here -->


    <string name="open"> </string>
    <string name="close"> </string>
    <string name="contact">"We will be more than happy to hear from you. Don't hesitate to contact us at ""smmbudget@gmail.com"" </string>


    <string name="Chinese_Food_Recipe">Dishes</string>
    <string name="Kung_Pao_Chicken">Kung Pao Chicken</string>
    <string name="Kung_Pao_Chicken_Recipe">
        <br><b> Ingredients : \n</b>\n</br>
        <br>- 2 tablespoons cornstarch, dissolved in 2 tablespoons water\n </br>
        <br>- 2 tablespoons white wine, divided\n </br>
        <br>- 2 tablespoons soy sauce, divided\n</br>
        <br>- 2 tablespoons sesame oil, divided\n </br>
        <br>- 1 pound skinless, boneless chicken, breast halves - cut into chunks\n</br>
        <br>- 1 ounce hot chili paste\n</br>
        <br>- 2 teaspoons brown sugar\n</br>
        <br>- 1 teaspoon distilled white vinegar\n</br>
        <br>- 1 (8 ounce) can water chestnuts\n</br>
        <br>- 4 ounces chopped peanuts\n</br>
        <br>- 4 green onions, chopped\n</br>
        <br>- 1 tablespoon chopped garlic\n\n</br>

        "---------------------\n\n"

        "Directions : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "Combine water and cornstarch in a cup; set aside.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "Combine 1 tablespoon wine, 1 tablespoon soy sauce, 1 tablespoon sesame oil, and 1 tablespoon cornstarch/water mixture in a large glass bowl. Add chicken pieces and toss to coat. Cover the dish and refrigerate for about 30 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "Combine remaining 1 tablespoon wine, 1 tablespoon soy sauce, 1 tablespoon sesame oil, and remaining cornstarch/water mixture in a medium bowl. Whisk in chili paste, brown sugar, and vinegar. Add water chestnuts, peanuts, green onions, and garlic and toss to coat.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "Transfer water chestnut mixture to a medium skillet. Heat slowly over medium heat until aromatic.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "Meanwhile, transfer chicken from marinade into a large skillet; cook over medium-high heat, stirring, until chicken is cooked through and juices run clear.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "Combine water chestnut mixture and sautéed chicken together in one skillet. Adjust heat and simmer together until sauce thickens.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="Mapo_Tofu">Mapo Tofu</string>
    <string name="Mapo_Tofu_Recipe">
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- Yield: 4 servings (about 4 cups)\n\n"
        "- 16ounces medium or medium-firm tofu (if unavailable, go with firm)\n"
        "- 1rounded teaspoon Sichuan peppercorns\n"
        "- 3tablespoons canola oil\n"
        "- 6ounces ground beef or pork (preferably 80 or 85 percent lean), roughly chopped to loosen\n"
        "- 2½ to 3tablespoons doubanjiang (fermented chile bean sauce or paste)\n"
        "- 1tablespoon douchi (fermented black beans, optional)\n"
        "- 1teaspoon minced fresh ginger\n"
        "- ½teaspoon red-pepper flakes (optional)\n"
        "- 2teaspoons regular soy sauce\n"
        "- 1rounded teaspoon granulated sugar, plus more if needed\n"
        "- Fine sea salt\n"
        "- 2large scallions, trimmed and cut on a sharp bias into thin, 2-inch-long pieces\n"
        "- 1½tablespoons cornstarch dissolved in 3 tablespoons water\n"
        "- Cooked white rice, for serving\n\n"

        "------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "Prepare the tofu: Cut the tofu into ¾-inch cubes and put into a bowl. Bring a kettle of water to a rolling boil. Turn off the heat and when the boiling subsides, pour hot water over the tofu to cover. Set aside for 15 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "Meanwhile, in a large (14-inch) wok or (12-inch) skillet over medium heat, toast the peppercorns for 2 to 3 minutes, until super fragrant and slightly darkened. (A wisp of smoke is normal.) Let cool briefly, then pound with a mortar and pestle, or pulse in a spice grinder.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "Set a strainer over a measuring cup, then add the tofu to drain; reserve 1½ cups of the soaking water, discarding the rest. Set the tofu and reserved soaking water near the stove with the peppercorns and other prepped ingredients for swift cooking.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "Reheat the wok or skillet over high. When hot — you can flick water in and it should sizzle and evaporate within seconds — swirl in the oil to evenly coat, then add the meat. Stir and mash into cooked and crumbly pieces, 1 to 2 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "Add 2½ tablespoons doubanjiang, the douchi (if using), ginger and red-pepper flakes (if using). Cook about 2 minutes longer, stirring constantly, until things are vivid reddish brown. Add the soy sauce and sugar, stir to combine, then add the tofu. Gently stir or shake the pan to combine the ingredients without breaking up the tofu much.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "Add the reserved 1½ cups soaking water, bring to a vigorous simmer, and cook for about 3 minutes, agitating the pan occasionally, to let the tofu absorb the flavors of the sauce.\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "Slightly lower the heat and taste the sauce. If needed, add the remaining ½ tablespoon of doubanjiang for heat, a pinch of salt for savoriness, or a sprinkle of sugar to tame heat.\n\n"
        "STEP - 08\n"
        "Add the scallions and stir to combine. Stir in the cornstarch slurry, then stir in enough to the mapo tofu to thicken to a soupy rather than a gravy-like finish. Sprinkle in the ground peppercorns, give the mixture one last stir to incorporate, then transfer to a shallow bowl. Serve immediately with lots of hot rice.\n\n"

    </string>

    <string name="Sweet_and_Sour_Pork">Sweet and Sour Pork</string>
    <string name="Sweet_and_Sour_Pork_Recipe">
        "INGREDIENTS :  \n\n"
        "- 1 pound pork butt, cut into 1 inch cubes\n\n"
        "Marinade : \n\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon soy sauce\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon salt\n"
        "- ¼ teaspoon white sugar\n"
        "- 1 egg white\n"
        "- 2 green onions, chopped\n\n"
        "Frying : \n\n"
        "- 1 quart vegetable oil for frying\n"
        "- ½ cup cornstarch\n\n"
        "Stir-Fried Vegetables : \n\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon vegetable oil\n"
        "- 3 stalks celery, cut into 1/2 inch pieces\n"
        "- 1 medium green bell pepper, cut into 1 inch pieces\n"
        "- 1 medium onion, cut into wedges\n"
        "- 1 pinch white sugar, or to taste\n"
        "- salt to taste\n"
        "- 1 ¼ cups water, divided\n"
        "- ¾ cup white sugar\n"
        "- ⅓ cup apple cider vinegar\n"
        "- ¼ cup ketchup\n"
        "- ½ teaspoon soy sauce\n"
        "- ¼ teaspoon salt\n"
        "- 1 (8 ounce) can pineapple chunks, undrained\n"
        "- 2 tablespoons cornstarch\n\n"

        "---------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "Place cubed pork in a medium bowl and season with soy sauce, salt, and sugar for marinade. Add egg white and green onions and mix until well-combined. Cover and place in the refrigerator for at least 1 hour.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "Heat 1 quart oil to 365 degrees F (185 degrees C) in a large, heavy saucepan or deep fryer.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "Coat pork with cornstarch and fry in hot oil until evenly browned, about 10 minutes. Drain on paper towels and set aside.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "Heat oil for vegetables in a wok over medium heat. Stir in celery, bell pepper, and onion; cook until tender, about 5 minutes. Season with pinch of sugar and salt. Remove from heat and set aside.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "Mix 1 cup water, 3/4 cup sugar, apple cider vinegar, ketchup, soy sauce, and salt in a large saucepan; bring to a boil over high heat.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "Stir in cooked pork, celery mixture, and pineapple chunks with juice. Return to a boil, then mix in remaining 1/4 cup water and cornstarch. Cook until thickened and warmed through, about 2 minutes.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="Peaking_Duck">Peking Duck</string>
    <string name="Peaking_Duck_Recipe">
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 1 (4 pound) whole duck, dressed\n"
        "- ½ teaspoon ground cinnamon\n"
        "- ½ teaspoon ground ginger\n"
        "- ¼ teaspoon ground nutmeg\n"
        "- ¼ teaspoon ground white pepper\n"
        "- ⅛ teaspoon ground cloves\n"
        "- 3 tablespoons soy sauce, divided\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon honey\n"
        "- 5 green onions, divided\n"
        "- ½ cup plum jam\n"
        "- ¼ cup finely chopped chutney\n"
        "- 1 ½ teaspoons sugar\n"
        "- 1 ½ teaspoons distilled white vinegar\n"
        "- 1 orange, sliced in rounds\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon chopped fresh parsley, for garnish\n\n"

        "-----------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "Rinse duck inside and out; pat dry. Cut off tail and discard.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "Mix together cinnamon, ginger, nutmeg, white pepper, and cloves in a small bowl. Sprinkle 1 teaspoon spice mixture into cavity of duck. Stir 1 tablespoon soy sauce into remaining spice mixture and rub evenly over entire outside of duck. Cut 1 green onion in half and tuck it inside cavity. Cover and refrigerate duck for at least 2 hours or up to overnight.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "Place duck breast-side up on a rack set in a wok or pot. Steam for 1 hour, adding more water as it evaporates. Lift duck with two large spoons to drain juices and green onion. Place duck breast-side up in a roasting pan and prick skin all over with a fork.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "Preheat the oven to 375 degrees F (190 degrees C).\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "Roast duck in the preheated oven for 30 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "Mix together remaining 2 tablespoons soy sauce and honey in a small bowl. Brush honey mixture onto duck.\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "Increase the oven temperature to 500 degrees F (260 degrees C). Roast until skin is richly browned, about 5 minutes. Do not allow skin to char.\n\n"
        "STEP - 08\n"
        "Mix together plum jam, chutney, sugar, and vinegar in a small serving bowl. Chop remaining green onions and place them into a separate bowl.\n\n"
        "STEP - 09\n"
        "Place whole duck onto a serving platter and garnish with orange slices and fresh parsley. Serve with plum sauce and chopped green onions.\n\n"

    </string>

    <string name="Fried_Rice">Fried Rice</string>
    <string name="Fried_Rice_Recipe">
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- ⅔ cup chopped baby carrots\n"
        "- ½ cup frozen green peas\n"
        "- 2 tablespoons vegetable oil\n"
        "- 1 clove garlic, minced, or to taste (Optional)\n"
        "- 2 large eggs\n"
        "- 3 cups leftover cooked white rice\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon soy sauce, or more to taste\n"
        "- 2 teaspoons sesame oil, or to taste\n\n"

        "-----------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "Assemble Ingredients.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "Place carrots in a small saucepan and cover with water. Bring to a low boil and cook for 3 to 5 minutes. Stir in peas, then immediately drain in a colander.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "Heat a wok over high heat. Pour in vegetable oil, then stir in carrots, peas, and garlic; cook for about 30 seconds. Add eggs; stir quickly to scramble eggs with vegetables\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "Stir in cooked rice. Add soy sauce and toss rice to coat. Drizzle with sesame oil and toss again.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "Serve hot and enjoy!\n\n"
        "Cook's Notes : \n\n"
        "If you don't have any leftover cooked rice, here's how to make it: Combine 4 cups water and 2 cups white rice in a saucepan; bring to a boil. Reduce heat, cover, and simmer until rice is tender and water has been absorbed, 20 to 25 minutes. Remove from the heat and let cool to room temperature. For the best fried rice results, cover and refrigerate the rice, 8 hours to overnight, before using in this recipe.\n\n"

    </string>

    <string name="Congee">Peking Duck</string>
    <string name="Congee_Resipe">
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 7 cups chicken or vegetable stock\n"
        "- 1 cup raw long-grain white rice, rinsed\n"
        "- 1/2 teaspoon kosher or sea salt, plus more for seasoning\n"
        "- 1-inch knob of ginger, peeled and sliced thin\n"
        "- Sliced scallions, for garnish\n"
        "- Sesame seed oil or soy sauce, for serving (optional)\n\n"

        "---------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "Gather the ingredients.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "In a large pot, add stock, rice, salt, and ginger. Bring the mixture to a boil, then reduce the heat to a low simmer. Stir occasionally so that the rice doesn't clump or stick at the bottom.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "Simmer the congee for about 1 hour or until the congee is thickened and creamy. Add salt to taste.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "Serve the congee hot with scallions, sesame seed oil, and soy sauce.\n\n"
        "NOTES :\n"
        "As the congee cools, it will become thicker. Add additional stock or water if necessary to make the congee to your desired thickness.\n\n"

    </string>

    <string name="General_Tsos_Chicken">General Tso\'s Chicken</string>
    <string name="General_Tsos_Chiken_Recipe">
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "Chicken : \n"
        "- 4 cups vegetable oil for frying\n"
        "- 1 large egg\n"
        "- 1 ½ pounds skinless, boneless chicken thighs, cut into 1 1/2-inch pieces\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon salt\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon white sugar\n"
        "- 1 pinch white pepper\n"
        "- 1 cup cornstarch\n\n"
        "Sauce :\n"
        "- 2 tablespoons vegetable oil\n"
        "- 3 tablespoons chopped green onion\n"
        "- 1 clove garlic, minced\n"
        "- 6 dried whole red chilies\n"
        "- 1 strip orange zest\n"
        "- ½ cup white sugar\n"
        "- ¼ cup soy sauce\n"
        "- 3 tablespoons chicken broth\n"
        "- 2 tablespoons peanut oil\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon rice vinegar\n"
        "- 2 teaspoons sesame oil\n"
        "- ¼ teaspoon ground ginger\n"
        "- 2 teaspoons cornstarch\n"
        "- ¼ cup water\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "Heat vegetable oil in a deep-fryer or large saucepan to 375 degrees F (190 degrees C).\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "Whisk egg in large mixing bowl. Add chicken, salt, sugar, and pepper; mix well. Mix in cornstarch, a little bit at a time, until chicken is well coated.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "Working in batches, carefully drop one piece of chicken at a time into the hot oil. Fry until chicken turns golden brown and begins to float, about 3 minutes. Remove chicken to a plate and allow to cool as you fry the next batch.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "Once all of the chicken has been fried, refry the chicken, starting with the batch that was cooked first. Fry each batch until chicken turns deep golden brown, about 2 minutes more. Drain on a paper towel-lined plate.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "Prepare sauce: Heat vegetable oil in a wok or large skillet over high heat. Stir in green onion, garlic, whole chiles, and orange zest. Cook and stir until garlic turns golden and chiles brighten, 1 to 2 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "Add sugar, soy sauce, chicken broth, peanut oil, rice vinegar, sesame oil, and ginger; bring to a boil and cook for 3 minutes. Whisk 2 teaspoons of cornstarch in water until dissolved. Stir into the boiling sauce. Return to a boil and cook until the sauce thickens and is no longer cloudy from the cornstarch, about 1 minute.\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "Stir chicken into the boiling sauce. Reduce heat to low and cook until chicken is heated through and has absorbed some of the sauce, about 3 minutes.\n\n"

    </string>

    <string name="Wonton_Soup">Wonton Soup</string>
    <string name="Wonton_Soup_Recipe">
    "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
    "Wontons :\n"
    "- ½ pound boneless pork loin, coarsely chopped\n"
    "- 2 ounces peeled shrimp, finely chopped\n"
    "- 1 tablespoon Chinese rice wine\n"
    "- 1 tablespoon light soy sauce\n"
    "- 1 teaspoon brown sugar\n"
    "- 1 teaspoon finely chopped green onions\n"
    "- 1 teaspoon chopped fresh ginger root\n"
    "- 24 (3.5 inch square) wonton wrappers\n\n"
    "Soup : \n"
    "- 3 cups chicken stock\n"
    "- 2 tablespoons finely chopped green onions\n\n"

    "--------------------------\n\n"

    "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
    "STEP - 01\n"
    "Make the wontons: Mix pork, shrimp, rice wine, soy sauce, brown sugar, green onions, and ginger together in a large bowl until well combined. Let stand for 25 to 30 minutes.\n\n"
    "STEP - 02\n"
    "Spoon about 1 teaspoon filling onto the center of a wonton wrapper. Moisten all four wrapper edges with water and fold over filling to make a triangle; press the edges firmly to seal. Bring left and right corners together above filling; overlap the tips of these corners, moisten with water, and press together to seal. Repeat until all wrappers have been filled and sealed.\n\n"
    "STEP - 03\n"
    "Make the soup: Bring chicken stock to a rolling boil in a pot. Gently drop in wontons and cook for 5 minutes.\n\n"
    "STEP - 04\n"
    "Ladle into bowls and garnish with green onions.\n\n"
    "Tips :\n"
    "Uncooked wontons will keep in the freezer for up to 2 months if they're wrapped well. Thaw them first if you're frying them, but if you're boiling them, drop frozen wontons into boiling broth and cool for 7 minutes.\n"
    "To Fry Wontons: Heat 2 to 3 cups oil in a wok until hot. Deep-fry wontons in batches until golden, 2 to 3 minutes per side. Drain on a paper towel-lined plate. Serve with duck sauce (plum sauce) or any dipping sauce.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="Beef_with_Broccoli_Recipe">
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- ⅓ cup oyster sauce\n"
        "- ⅓ cup sherry\n"
        "- 2 teaspoons toasted sesame oil\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon soy sauce\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon white sugar\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon cornstarch\n"
        "- ¾ pound beef round steak, cut into 1/8-inch thick strips\n"
        "- 3 tablespoons vegetable oil, plus more if needed\n"
        "- 1 thin slice of fresh ginger root\n"
        "- 1 clove garlic, peeled and smashed\n"
        "- 1 pound broccoli, cut into florets\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "Whisk oyster sauce, sherry, sesame oil, soy sauce, sugar, and cornstarch together in a bowl; stir until sugar has dissolved.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "Place steak in a shallow bowl. Pour oyster sauce mixture over meat and stir to coat; cover and marinate in the refrigerator for at least 30 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "Heat vegetable oil in a wok or large skillet over medium-high heat. Add ginger and garlic; let sizzle for about 1 minute to flavor oil, then remove and discard. Stir in broccoli. Toss and stir until bright green and almost tender, 5 to 7 minutes. Remove broccoli from the wok and set aside.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "Add a little more oil to the wok, if needed, then add beef with marinade. Stir and toss until sauce thickens and turns shiny and meat is no longer pink, about 5 minutes. Return broccoli to the wok; stir until heated through, about 3 minutes.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="Beef_Noodle_Soup_Recipe">
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 1 pound cubed beef stew meat\n"
        "- 1 cup chopped onion\n"
        "- 1 cup chopped celery\n"
        "- 1 cup chopped carrots\n"
        "- ¼ cup beef bouillon granules\n"
        "- ¼ teaspoon dried parsley\n"
        "- 1 pinch ground black pepper\n"
        "- 5 ¾ cups water\n"
        "- 2 ½ cups frozen egg noodles\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "Sauté stew meat, onion, and celery in a large saucepan over medium-high heat until meat is browned on all sides, about 5 minutes\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "Stir in carrots, then season with bouillon, parsley, and pepper. Stir in water and add egg noodles.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "Bring to a boil, reduce heat to low, and simmer for 30 minutes.\n\n"

    </string>

    <string name="Salt_and_Pepper_Shrimp_Recipe">"Servings : 3  "
        "| Cook Time: 30 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 1 lb frozen shrimp(455 g), peeled and deveined, tails left on\n"
        "- 1 cup cornstarch(125 g)\n"
        "- 3 cups oil(720 mL)\n"
        "- 6 cloves garlic, chopped\n"
        "- 2 tablespoons fresh ginger, sliced\n"
        "- 2 teaspoons red pepper flakes\n"
        "- 2 teaspoons salt\n"
        "- 3 teaspoons black pepper\n"
        "- ¼ cup scallions(25 g), sliced\n"
        "- white rice, cooked, for serving\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "Set a wire rack over a baking sheet.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "Add the shrimp to a medium bowl. Cover with cold water and let sit until thawed, about 10 minutes\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "Drain the thawed shrimp on paper towels and pat dry.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "Place the cornstarch in a large bowl. Add the shrimp and toss until well-coated.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "Heat the oil in a wok or large pan until it reaches 400°F (200°C).\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "Add the garlic and fry for 40 seconds-1 minute, until golden brown. Remove the garlic with a strainer or slotted spoon and drain on paper towels.\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "Fry the shrimp, about 6 at a time, for 2 minutes, or until light golden brown. Transfer to the wire rack to drain.\n\n"
        "STEP - 08\n"
        "In a clean wok or large pan, add the ginger and red pepper flakes and toast for 2 minutes, until the ginger is starting to brown.\n\n"
        "STEP - 09\n"
        "Add the shrimp and toss to combine. Season with the salt and pepper and toss until well-coated.\n\n"
        "STEP - 10\n"
        "Transfer the shrimp to a plate and garnish with the scallions and fried garlic.\n\n"
        "STEP - 11\n"
        "Serve with rice and Enjoy!\n\n"

    </string>

    <string name="Egg_Drop_Soup_Recipe">"Servings : 1"
        "| Cook Time: 15 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 1 cup chicken broth\n"
        "- ¼ teaspoon soy sauce\n"
        "- ¼ teaspoon sesame oil\n"
        "- 2 teaspoons water (Optional)\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon cornstarch (Optional)\n"
        "- 1 egg, beaten\n"
        "- 1 drop yellow food coloring (Optional)\n"
        "- ½ teaspoon ground white pepper (Optional)\n"
        "- ⅛ teaspoon salt (Optional)\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon chopped fresh chives\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "Combine chicken broth, soy sauce, and sesame oil in a small saucepan over medium heat; bring to a boil.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "Stir water and cornstarch together in a small bowl until cornstarch is dissolved; pour into boiling broth. Stir in food coloring. Slowly pour in beaten egg, stirring constantly; season with white pepper and salt. Serve hot, garnished with fresh chives.\n\n"

    </string>

    <string name="Douhua_Tofu_Pudding_Recipe">"Servings: 3"
        "| Cook Time: 30 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 0.5 cup soy beans\n"
        "- 750 ml water\n"
        "- 1.5 g GDL , around 1 tablespoon (no sweeping)\n"
        "- sugar to taste\n\n"
        "Brown sugar syrup : \n"
        "- 0.5 cup brown sugar\n"
        "- 0.5 cup water\n"
        "- 0.5 thumb piece ginger , peeled and shredded\n"
        "Sichuan hot Style for each serving :\n"
        "-0.5 tsp. chili oil\n"
        "-0.5 tsp. light soy sauce\n"
        "-0.5 tbsp. chopped Zhai Cai\n"
        "-0.5 tbsp. ginger and garlic water\n"
        "-chopped scallion and coriander to taste\n\n"
        "Northern Style : \n"
        "-0.5 tbsp. cooking oil\n"
        "-25g pork belly\n"
        "-0.5 thumb ginger , cut into small shreds\n"
        "-0.5 clove garlic , shredded\n"
        "-5 hydrated wood ear mushroom , cut into small shreds\n"
        "-1 fresh shiitake mushroom , cut into slices\n"
        "-2 oyster mushrooms , thinly sliced and then shredded\n"
        "-1 cups water\n"
        "-1 tbsp. light soy sauce\n"
        "-0.5 tbsp. dark soy sauce\n"
        "-0.5 tbsp. cornstarch , whisked with 2 tablespoons of water\n"
        "-salt and pepper to taste\n"
        "-0.5 egg\n"
        "-salt if necessary , note 1\n\n"



        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Wash the soy beans and then soak the soy beans overnight until softened. Transfer to a blender and add water. Blend until very smooth\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Place a gauze on a strainer and then strain the soy milk.  Bring the soy milk to a boil. Watch carefully since it overflows easily. Skin off the bubbles on the surface. Remove from heat and rest for 2 minutes until the temperature drops around 80 degree C to 90 degree C\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Whisk GDL with water in a small bowl (read the instructions on the package for the detailed amount). Gently stir the GDL water in the soy milk. Then rest for 15 to 20 minutes until firms.\n\n"
        "How to serve| Sweet version : \n\n"
        "- Option 1: Serve with white sugar directly\n\n- Option 2: Simmer brown sugar with ginger slices for 5 minutes and drizzle the syrup with tofu pudding.\n\n"
        "How to serve |Northern Version : \n\n"
        "- Add some oil in pan and fry pork belly until slightly browned. Add wood ear mushroom, oyster mushroom and shiitake mushroom. Fry until soft.\n\n"
        "- Add around 2 cups of water, soy sauce (dark soy sauce and light soy sauce). Place cornstarch water in and simmer for 5 to 7 minutes until the sauce is almost thickened.\n\n"
        "- Drizzle egg liquid in. Continue cooking until well combined. Add salt if necessary. Top the gravy with tofu pudding.\n\n"
        "How to serve |Sichuan Style : \n\n"
        "- To make ginger and garlic water | add ½ cup hot water into 1 tablespoon of minced ginger and 1 tablespoon of minced garlic. Set until cool down.\n\n"
        "- Fry soaked soy beans with cold oil until golden brown. You can simply replace this with toasted peanuts or other crispy nuts.\n\n"
        "- How to assemble| add chopped Zha Cai, light soy sauce, chili oil, garlic ginger water, spring onion and coriander. Serve hot.\n\n"
        "NOTES : \n"
        "- You can test the gravy and see whether a pinch of salt is needed (mostly based on the saltness of the soy sauce and your own taste preference).\n\n"
    </string>


    <string name="Turnip_Cake_Recipe">"Servings: 6"
        "| Cook Time: 1 hour\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 20 ounces daikon radish (grated)\n"
        "- 1 to 1 1/2 cups water\n"
        "- vegetable oil\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon dried shrimp (washed, soaked and chopped)\n"
        "- 3-5 dried shiitake mushrooms (washed, soaked, and chopped)\n"
        "- 1 Chinese sausage (diced)\n"
        "- 1 scallion (chopped)\n"
        "- 1 1/4 cups rice flour\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon cornstarch\n"
        "- ½ teaspoon salt\n"
        "- ½ teaspoon sugar\n"
        "- white pepper (to taste)\n"
        "- Oyster sauce (for dipping, optional)\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Add the grated turnip and 1 cup water to a wok or large pan, and bring to a simmer. Simmer for about 10 minutes, stirring occasionally so the turnip does not brown. The turnip will produce liquid, some of which will evaporate. You will have liquid left in the wok with the radish that you will also use. Scoop the cooked turnip into a large mixing bowl to cool. Pour any remaining liquid in the wok into a measuring cup, and add water until you have a total of 1 cup of liquid. Add it to the mixing bowl with the cooked turnip.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Clean your wok or pan and place it over medium heat. Add a couple tablespoons oil. Add the shrimp, mushrooms, and sausage, and cook for about 5 minutes. Stir in the chopped scallion and remove from the heat to cool.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Add rice flour, cornstarch, salt, sugar, and white pepper to the mixing bowl with the radish and cooking liquid. Mix well until the dry ingredients are well-incorporated. Add in the cooked shrimp, mushrooms and sausage, and be sure to scrape the oil from the pan into the batter. If you like your radish cake soft, you can add another 1/4 cup or more of boiling water to the batter. If you feel the batter is too thin, return it to the wok on low heat to thicken the batter while stirring. Mix well and let sit for 15 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Give the batter a final stir, and pour it into a well-oiled loaf pan. Place the pan into a steamer with plenty of water and steam over medium-high heat for 50 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Remove the pan from the steamer and let your turnip cake set for about 30 minutes. Once cooled, loosen the sides with a spatula and turn it out onto a cutting board. It should come out quite easily.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "- Use a sharp knife dipped in water to slice ½-inch thick pieces. I know people who’d enjoy it just like that, but most people pan-fry the turnip cake first. Add a couple tablespoons oil to a non-stick or seasoned cast iron pan over medium heat. Fry the cakes on both sides until golden and crispy. Serve with oyster sauce!\n\n"
        "NOTE : \n"
        "- You can also make this turnip cake in advance, refrigerate it in the loaf pan, and slice/fry later. If you’ve refrigerated turnip cakes that you’ve already fried, the best way to reheat them is to re-fry them in a pan.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Beef_and_Black_Bean_Sauce_Recipe">"Servings: 4"
        "| Cook Time: 30 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 2 x 250g rump steaks\n"
        "- 1 tbsp cornflour\n"
        "- 2 tbsp sesame oil\n"
        "- 1 large white onion, cut into thin wedges\n"
        "- 1 red pepper, deseeded and sliced\n"
        "- 1 green pepper, deseeded and sliced\n"
        "- 2 fat garlic cloves, crushed\n"
        "- 1 thumb-sized piece ginger, peeled and grated\n"
        "- 1-2 red chillies, finely chopped\n"
        "- 5 tbsp black bean sauce\n"
        "- 1 tbsp rice wine vinegar\n"
        "- 2 tsp sugar\n"
        "- sticky rice, to serve\n"
        "- coriander leaves, to serve (optional)\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Remove the thick layer of fat running down the side of the steaks and discard. Slice the steak into 1cm-thick, long strips and toss with the cornflour and some seasoning.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Heat the oil in a large frying pan or wok over a high heat then add the steak, frying for 3-5 mins or until golden brown on the outside. Remove with a slotted spoon and transfer to a plate\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Add the onion and peppers to the pan and fry for 6-7 mins or until beginning to soften. Stir through the garlic, ginger and chilli and cook for a further min. Return the beef to the pan and stir through the black bean sauce, rice wine vinegar, sugar and 2 tbsp water to loosen a little. Bring to a simmer and then remove from the heat.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Serve the stir-fry in deep bowls with mounds of sticky rice and top with coriander, if you like.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Sushi_Recipe">"Servings: 8"
        "| Cook Time: 1 hr 5 mins\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 1 ⅓ cups water\n"
        "- ⅔ cup uncooked short-grain white rice\n"
        "- 3 tablespoons rice vinegar\n"
        "- 3 tablespoons white sugar\n"
        "- 1 ½ teaspoons salt\n"
        "- 4 sheets nori seaweed sheets\n"
        "- ½ pound imitation crabmeat, flaked\n"
        "- 1 avocado - peeled, pitted, and sliced\n"
        "- ½ cucumber, peeled, cut into small strips\n"
        "- 2 tablespoons pickled ginger\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Preheat the oven to 300 degrees F (150 degrees C).\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Bring water to a boil in a medium pot; stir in rice. Reduce heat to medium-low, cover, and simmer until rice is tender and water has been absorbed, 20 to 25 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Mix rice vinegar, sugar, and salt in a small bowl. Gently stir into cooked rice in the pot and set aside.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Lay nori sheets on a baking sheet.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Heat nori in the preheated oven until warm, 1 to 2 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "- Center 1 nori sheet on a bamboo sushi mat. Use wet hands to spread a thin layer of rice on top. Arrange 1/4 of the crabmeat, avocado, cucumber, and pickled ginger over rice in a line down the center. Lift one end of the mat and roll it tightly over filling to make a complete roll. Repeat with remaining ingredients.\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "- Use a wet, sharp knife to cut each roll into 4 to 6 slices.\n\n"
        "TIPS : \n"
        "- If you do not have a bamboo sushi mat, the easiest way to roll sushi is with a clean dish towel.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Tempura_Recipe">"Servings: 6"
        "| Cook Time: 15 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 1 cup all-purpose flour\n"
        "- 1 large egg\n"
        "- 1 cup water\n"
        "- Ice cubes, for chilling the water\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Gather the ingredients.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- In a small bowl, sift the flour once or twice to remove any clumps and to make it light and soft. Set aside.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- In a separate medium bowl, gently beat egg until the yolk and egg whites are just barely incorporated.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Combine the water and ice cubes in a cup. Using a strainer, strain the water (you should have 1 cup of ice-cold water) and add it to the bowl with the beaten egg. Make sure you do not actually add ice cubes to the tempura batter.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Add the sifted flour into the bowl with the egg and water mixture and lightly combine the flour using chopsticks. Be careful not to overmix the batter; it should be a little lumpy.\n\n"
    </string>


    <string name="Ramen_Recipe">"Servings: 4"
        "| Cook Time: 23 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon sesame oil\n"
        "- 2 teaspoons garlic, minced\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon ginger paste\n"
        "- 1 1/2 cups mushrooms, sliced\n"
        "- 4 cups chicken stock or broth of choice\n"
        "- 4 cups water\n"
        "- 1/4 cup soy sauce\n"
        "- 5-6 leaves baby bokchoy, chopped or left whole\n"
        "- 4 packs of ramen noodles throw out those seasoning packets!!\n"
        "- salt and pepper to taste\n\n"
        "Toppings : \n"
        "- 1 pound grilled chicken, sliced\n"
        "- 2 soft boiled egg, halved\n"
        "- 1/4 cup green onions, sliced\n"
        "- sesame seeds, for garnish\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Add the sesame oil into a large pot and heat over medium heat. Add in the garlic and ginger and sauté for 30 seconds until fragrant.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Add in the sliced mushrooms and cook for 3-5 minutes or until softened\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Pour in the chicken stock, water, and soy sauce.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Bring to a boil and simmer for about 5 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Add the boychoy and simmer for an additional 2 minutes to soften the leaves.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "- Remove the pot from the heat. Place the ramen noodles in the hot pot of broth. Allow the noodles to sit for ONLY a couple of minutes until they loosen and soften up. The noodles will soften quickly, so this should be done right before serving.\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "- Divide the ramen, veggies, and broth evenly into bowls.\n\n"
        "STEP - 08\n"
        "- Top the ramen with sliced grilled chicken and soft boiled eggs. Garnish with toppings of choice and enjoy!\n\n"


    </string>


    <string name="Miso_Soup_Recipe">"Servings: 4"
        "| Cook Time: 15 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 4 cups water\n"
        "- 2 teaspoons dashi granules\n"
        "- 3 tablespoons miso paste\n"
        "- 1 (8 ounce) package silken tofu, diced\n"
        "- 2 green onions, sliced diagonally into 1/2 inch pieces\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Combine water and dashi granules in a medium saucepan over medium-high heat; bring to a boil. Reduce heat to medium and whisk in miso paste. Stir in tofu. Separate the layers of green onions, and add them to the soup. Simmer gently for 2 to 3 minutes before serving.\n\n"
        "TIPS : \n"
        "- Dashi is a basic stock used in Japanese cooking which is made by boiling dried kelp (seaweed) and dried bonito (fish). Instant dashi granules are sold in conveniently-sized jars or packets and vary in strength\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Teriyaki_Chicken_Recipe">"Servings: 4"
        "| Cook Time: 15 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 1.3 pounds (600 grams) skinless boneless chicken thighs, cut into 1 1/2-inch pieces\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon cooking oil\n"
        "- 1/4 cup low-sodium soy sauce\n"
        "- 3 tablespoons light brown sugar (or white granulated sugar)\n"
        "- 3 tablespoons cooking Sake ((rice wine vinegar or apple cider vinegar)\n"
        "- 2 tablespoons Mirin (optional white wine or dry sherry can be substituted)\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon sesame oil, optional (adds a wonderful flavour)\n"
        "- 2 teaspoons minced garlic (2 cloves garlic)*\n"
        "- 1 shallot/green onion stem, sliced to garnish\n"
        "- 4 cups broccoli florets, lightly steamed\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon cornstarch (or corn flour) mixed with 2 teaspoons water (ONLY IF NEEDED)\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Heat cooking oil in a large pan over medium heat. Stir fry chicken, stirring occasionally until lightly browned and crisp.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- In a small jug or bowl whisk together the soy sauce, sugar, Sake/vinegar, Mirin and sesame oil to combine. Set aside.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Add the garlic to the centre of the pan and saute until lightly fragrant (about 30 seconds). Pour in the sauce and allow to cook, while stirring, until the sauce thickens into a beautiful shiny glaze (about 2-3 minutes).*\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Add in the steamed broccoli. Garnish with green onion (or shallot) slices and serve over steamed rice.\n\n"
        "Tips :\n"
        "- Replace garlic for 1/2 teaspoon minced ginger. You can also use both if you wish.\n\n"
        "- If for some reason your sauce has not thickened, quickly whisk in the cornstarch/water mixture and continue stirring until syrupy.\n\n"
        "- Alternatively, if sauce is too thick, add water in tablespoon increments until reaching your desired thickness.\n\n"
    </string>


    <string name="Pork_Tonkatsu_Recipe">"Servings: 4"
        "| Cook Time: 30 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 4 slices pork loin or tenderloin, each about 1/2-inch thick and 5 ounces\n"
        "- Salt and freshly ground black pepper\n"
        "- Salt and freshly ground black pepper \n"
        "- Flour for dredging\n"
        "- 2 eggs, lightly beaten\n"
        "- 2 cups panko (bread crumbs)\n"
        "- Vegetable oil for pan frying\n"
        "- Shredded Napa cabbage, for serving\n"
        "- Lemon wedges, for garnish\n"
        "- Tonkatsu sauce, for dipping\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Slash the fat rimming one side of the loin cutlet to keep the meat from curling when deepfried. Pound to flatten to about 1/4 inch. Salt and pepper both sides of each cutlet. Dredge each in flour, then dip into beaten eggs and press into bread crumbs to coat both sides. \n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Heat a large skillet with about 1/2 inch of oil until hot. Lay 1 or 2 cutlets in the hot oil. Deep-fry until golden brown, about 5 to 7 minutes, turning them once or twice. Drain the cutlets on paper towels and cut the pork into bite-size strips that can be eaten with chopsticks. \n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Arrange the pork on a platter lined with the shredded cabbage, and garnish with lemon wedges. Serve the sauce on the side for dipping, or pour it over the pork and cabbage.\n\n"
        "TURKEY TONKATSU:n"
        "- Prepare the recipe for Pork Tonkatsu, using 4 turkey cutlets, each about 1/2inch thick, in place of the pork loin.\n\n"

    </string>

    <string name="Beef_Sukiyaki_Recipe">"Servings: 4"
        "| Cook Time: 45 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 1 ½ cups prepared dashi stock\n"
        "- ¾ cup soy sauce\n"
        "- ¾ cup mirin\n"
        "- ¼ cup white sugar\n"
        "- 8 ounces shirataki noodles\n"
        "- 3 tablespoons canola oil, divided\n"
        "- 1 pound beef top sirloin, thinly sliced\n"
        "- 1 medium onion, thinly sliced\n"
        "- 2 medium carrots, thinly sliced\n"
        "- 2 stalks celery, thinly sliced\n"
        "- 4 ounces sliced fresh mushrooms (button, shiitake, or enoki)\n"
        "- 5 green onions, cut into 2-inch pieces\n"
        "- 1 (14 ounce) package firm tofu, cut into cubes\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Combine dashi, soy sauce, mirin, and sugar in a bowl; set aside.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Soak noodles in boiling water for 1 minute. Drain, rinse under cold water, and drain again.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Heat 2 tablespoons oil in a pot over medium heat. Add beef; cook and stir until no longer pink, 2 to 3 minutes. Transfer beef to a plate.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Add remaining 1 tablespoon oil to the pot and heat over medium heat. Add onion, carrots, celery, and mushrooms; cook and stir until softened, about 4 minutes. Add dashi mixture, noodles, beef, tofu, and green onions; bring to a simmer.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Remove from the heat and ladle hot sukiyaki into four bowls.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Okonomiyaki_Recipe">"Servings: 2"
        "| Cook Time: 25 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 3 packed cups finely shredded cabbage, about ½ medium*\n"
        "- 1¼ cups chopped scallions, about 1 bunch\n"
        "- 1 cup panko breadcrumbs\n"
        "- ¾ teaspoon sea salt\n"
        "- 3 eggs, beaten\n"
        "- Extra-virgin olive oil, for brushing\n\n"
        "for serving : \n"
        "- Vegan Worcestershire sauce, (Annie’s recommended)\n"
        "- Mayo, (Sir Kensington’s or Kewpie recommended)\n"
        "- Sesame seeds\n"
        "- Pickled ginger\n"
        "- ½ sheet nori, sliced**\n"
        "- ½ cup microgreens, optional\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- In a large bowl, combine the cabbage, scallions, panko, and salt. Gently mix in the eggs. (Note: the mixture will be very loose and cabbagey, not like a flour pancake batter. If it's very dry, let it sit for 10 minutes).\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Heat a nonstick skillet over medium heat. Brush the skillet with olive oil and use a ¼ measuring cup to scoop the cabbage mixture into the skillet. (It's okey if it doesn't seem cohesive, it'll bind together as the egg cooks). Flatten gently with a spatula so that the mixture is about 1/2 inch thick. Cook 3 minutes per side, or until browned, turning the heat to low as needed. Repeat with the remaining mixture, wiping out the skillet and brushing more oil, as needed.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Drizzle the okonomiyaki with Worcestershire sauce and thin strips of squeezed mayo. Top with sesame seeds, pickled ginger, and nori. Sprinkle with microgreens, if desired. Serve hot.\n\n"
        "NOTES:\n"
        "- *I like to shred my cabbage on a mandoline to get thin, even-sized shreds. **Use scissors to cut nori into thin strips\n\n"


    </string>


    <string name="Chawanmushi_Recipe">"Servings: 2"
        "| Cook Time: 25 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 3 large eggs weigh 50g each\n"
        "- 1/2 tsp usukuchi soy sauce *1\n"
        "- 1 tsp mirin\n"
        "- 375 ml Dashi stock *2\n"
        "- 1 shiitake mushrooms\n"
        "- 3 slices carrot\n"
        "- 2 pieces of Kamaboko fish cake I used Naruto fish cake left over from making Ramen\n"
        "- 2 shurimps\n"
        "- Mitsuba to garnish Option, I did not have one so I used flat leaf parsley instead\n"
        "- 3 shells edamame\n"
        "- 9 Ginnan(gingko nuts)\n"
        "- mitsuba leaves to garnish *optional\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- cut off stem of shiitake mushrooms and cut it into thin slices and slice the carrot about 3mm(0.1inch) and cut out using cookie cutters. *3\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- slice Naruto fish cakes thinly and set aside in a large bowl eggs, soy sauce and mirin together with chopsticks and try not to whisk too much to avoid aerating egg.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Pour Dashi stock into the ball small amount at a time and mix with egg gradually.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Use a strainer, strain the egg mixture in order to achieve silky soft texture when it is steamed. divide the mixture into 3 tea cups(or mugs or ramekins) pour water about 3 cm (1.2 inch) high in a pot 20cm ( 7.9 inch)  in diameter and bring it to boil over high heat.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Once the water boiled, place tea cups in the pot and turn down to low heat. wrap the lid with a tea towel, so that water does not drip over the chawanmushi. *4\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "- Put lid on and steam about 5-7 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "- When the egg mixture nearly set, top with shrimp, naruto, shiitake mushrooms, edamame, carrot and Ginnan\n\n"
        "STEP - 08\n"
        "- steam farther 5-3minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 09\n"
        "- Turn the heat off leave the chawanmushi bowl in the pot for set farther 5 min. \n\n"
         "STEP - 09\n"
        "- Garnish with Mitsuba (*5 if you have) and serve\n\n"
         "NOTES :\n"
        "- *1 Usukuchi soy sauce is a types of soy sauce. lighter in colour but the salt content is higher than normal soy sauce.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Yakitori_Recipe">"Servings: 6"
        "| Cook Time: 15 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 1pound chicken livers, gizzards or boneless thigh meat\n"
        "- ½cup dark soy sauce or tamari\n"
        "- ¼cup mirin\n"
        "- 2tablespoons sake or dry sherry\n"
        "- 1tablespoon brown sugar\n"
        "- 2garlic cloves, peeled and smashed\n"
        "- ½teaspoon grated fresh ginger\n"
        "- Scallions, thinly sliced, for garnish\n\n"


        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Cut chicken into one-inch pieces and place in a shallow dish.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- In a small saucepan, combine soy sauce or tamari, mirin, sake or sherry, brown sugar, garlic and ginger. Bring to a simmer and cook for 7 minutes, until thickened. Reserve 2 tablespoons sauce for serving. Pour remaining sauce over chicken, cover, and chill for at least one hour (and up to 4 hours).\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- If using wooden or bamboo skewers, soak them in water for one hour. Preheat grill or broiler. Thread chicken pieces onto skewers, and grill or broil, turning halfway, for about 3 minutes for livers, 10 minutes for gizzards and 6 minutes for thighs. Serve drizzled with reserved sauce and garnished with scallions.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Gyoza_Recipe">"Servings: "
        "| Cook Time: 50 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 2 tbsp cornflour\n"
        "- 26 ready-made gyoza skins, defrosted if frozen (see tip)\n"
        "- 2-3 tbsp vegetable oil\n\n"
        "For the filling : \n"
        "- 4 spring onions, ends trimmed, roughly chopped\n"
        "- 2 large leaves of Savoy or pointed cabbages, hard stem removed, roughly chopped\n"
        "- a 1½cm piece of ginger, peeled and chopped\n"
        "- 1 garlic clove\n"
        "- 50g water chestnuts, about 5 (drained weight)\n"
        "- 2 tsp soy sauce\n"
        "- 2 tsp oyster sauce\n"
        "- 1 tsp cooking saké\n"
        "- ½ tsp sesame oil\n"
        "- 140g minced pork or chicken\n\n"
        "For the soy dipping sauce :\n"
        "- 2 tbsp soy sauce\n"
        "- 1 tbsp rice vinegar\n"
        "- 2 tsp sesame oil\n\n"
        "For the yuzu dipping sauce : \n"
        "- 2 tbsp soy sauce\n"
        "- 2 tbsp Yuzu juice\n"
        "- 2 tsp peanut oil\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Put the spring onions, cabbage, ginger and garlic in a food processor, and whizz to a fine mix (or finely chop by hand).\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Add the water chestnuts and pulse to chop, but not too finely – these will add a nice crunchy texture. Add the soy sauce, oyster sauce, sake, sesame oil and a pinch of salt, and whizz again.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Tip the ingredients into a bowl and add the minced pork or chicken. Mix by hand until well combined. Chill until ready to use.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Have a pot of water to hand. Sprinkle the cornflour onto a plate. To assemble the gyoza, hold the dumpling skin in the palm of one hand and put a heaped teaspoon of the filling onto the centre of the skin.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Dip your finger in the water and wipe around the edge of the skin – this will moisten it and help the edges stick together.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "- Bring the edges of the skin together. Pinch pleats along one side, then press each pleat against the opposite flat side of the skin. With each pinch make sure that you are sealing the parcel and keeping the filling in the centre. Put each gyoza onto the plate dusted with cornflour. Can be covered with cling film and chilled for up to 8 hrs.\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "- Cook the gyoza in batches. Heat a non-stick frying pan with 1 tbsp vegetable oil. Brush off any excess cornflour from the bases of the dumplings. Fry the gyoza on one side only – don’t turn them over, you just want one crispy side. They should be golden brown after about 2 mins.\n\n"
        "STEP - 08\n"
        "- Add a good splash of water to the pan and cover with a steaming lid or a large sheet of foil with a few holes poked in the top. Cook over a medium heat for 3-5 mins until the water has evaporated and the gyoza filling is cooked through. Set aside while you cook the rest.\n\n"
        "STEP - 09\n"
        "- Mix all the dipping sauce ingredients and serve alongside the dumplings in dipping bowls. You can serve with both or just one dipping sauce.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Nikujaga_Recipe">"Servings: 4"
        "| Cook Time: 40 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 150g sukiyaki beef\n"
        "- 450g potato\n"
        "- 1 onion\n"
        "- 150g carrots\n"
        "- 480ml water\n"
        "- 2 tbsp cooking sake\n"
        "- 1 tsp dashi stock\n"
        "- 1 tbsp sugar\n"
        "- 1 tbsp mirin\n"
        "- 2 tbsp soy sauce\n"
        "- vegetable oil\n"
        "- 4 servings Japanese rice\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Cut the ingredients: Start by cutting up 150g beef slices and 1 onion into thin slices. Peel 150g carrots and 450g potatoes and then chop into bite-size pieces.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Stir fry the vegetables: Warm some vegetable oil in a frying pan, then add the onions cook over a medium heat for a few moments before adding the meat and letting it cook. After that, add in the potatoes and carrots.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Add 480ml water, 2 tsp cooking sake and 1 tsp dashi stock: Bring to the boil, skim off any scum that forms, then cover and cook over a low heat for 10 minutes, simmering.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Add 1 tbsp sugar and 1 tbsp mirin: Cook for a further 5 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Add 2 tbsp soy sauce: Simmer for a further 5 minutes without the lid.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "- Serve and enjoy: Continue to simmer until the liquid is reduced, then your nikujaga is ready to enjoy. Serve with freshly boiled white rice.\n\n"
        "TIPS :\n"
        "- It doesn’t have to beef, you can also use pork for this recipe and it will still taste great.\n\n"
        "- Try adding some sliced spring onions before serving for more flavour. Shirataki konnyaku noodles or abura age fried tofu are also make delicious additions.\n\n"
    </string>


    <string name="Zaru_Soba_Recipe">"Servings: 2"
        "| Cook Time: 10 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 2 bundles (200g) soba noodles\n"
        "- shredded seaweed, toasted sesame flakes for garnish, optional\n"
        "- green onion, grated daikon, wasabi, and/or egg yolk for the dipping sauce, optional\n\n"
        "Dipping sauce : \n"
        "- 1 cup dashi see notes below\n"
        "- 1/4 cup soy sauce\n"
        "- 1/4 cup mirin\n"
        "- 1 tbsp sugar or to taste\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Add dashi, soy sauce, mirin, and sugar into a saucepan and mix to combine. Once the mixture comes to a boil, remove from heat and place in the fridge or freezer to cool.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Cook noodles according to package instructions. Drain the noodles in a strainer and rinse under cold running water to remove the excess starch. Shake well to drain, transfer to a plate, and garnish to your preference.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Pour the dipping sauce into a bowl and dress to your liking. Dip a portion of the noodles in the sauce and enjoy!\n\n"
        "NOTES :\n"
        "- To prepare dashi, add 1/2 tsp of instant dashi powder with 1 cup of water and mix to combine. You can also use low-sodium chicken stock, or use a 2:1 ratio of regular chicken stock and water. \n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- The dipping sauce is good for up to 2 weeks in the fridge when stored in an airtight container. If you prefer the sauce to be extra cold, place it in the freezer for a few minutes before serving or add a few ice cubes to the sauce. \n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Katsudon_Recipe">"Servings: 2"
        "| Cook Time: 40 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 2 center-cut (boneless pork chops, pounded down to a centimeter thick)\n"
        "- salt and pepper\n"
        "- flour (for dusting)\n"
        "- 1 egg\n"
        "- 1 cup panko\n"
        "- oil (for frying)\n"
        "- 1/2 cup dashi stock or chicken stock\n"
        "- 2 teaspoons sugar\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon soy sauce\n"
        "- 2 teaspoons Mirin\n"
        "- 2 large eggs\n"
        "- 1 medium onion (thinly sliced)\n"
        "- 2 servings steamed white rice\n"
        "- 1 scallion (chopped)\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Season the pounded pork chops with salt and pepper, and dust with a light, even coating of flour. In one shallow bowl, beat the egg. Put the panko into another shallow bowl.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Add thin, even layer of oil to a cast iron pan or skillet over medium heat. The oil is ready when you throw a panko breadcrumb into the oil and it sizzles. Dip the pork into the egg to coat. Transfer the pork to the panko and press it evenly into the meat to get a good coating.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Carefully lay the pork chops in the hot oil and cook for 5-6 minutes on one side, until golden brown. Flip and cook the other side for another 5-6 minutes. Drain on a plate lined with a paper towel.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- While the pork is resting, add the stock, sugar, soy sauce, and Mirin to a small bowl. In another bowl, lightly beat 2 eggs. Add a tablespoon of oil to a pan over medium heat, and add the sliced onion. Fry the onions until they’re translucent and slightly caramelized.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Pour the stock mixture over the onions. Slice your tonkatsu into pieces and place on top of the onions. Drizzle the egg over everything. Cook over medium low heat until the egg is just set. Serve over bowls of steamed rice, and garnish with scallions.\n\n"

    </string>

    <string name="Unagi_don_Recipe">"Servings: 1-2"
        "| Cook Time: 20 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "unagi sauce : \n"
        "- 2 ½ tbsp sugar\n"
        "- 1 ½ tbsp cooking sake\n"
        "- 4 tbsp soy sauce\n"
        "- 4 tbsp mirin\n"
        "- 200g rice\n"
        "- 260ml water\n"
        "- 2 eel fillets, skin-on\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Make the sauce: Combine the 4 tbsp mirin and 1 ½ tbsp cooking sake in a small saucepan and bring to the boil. Reduce the heat and add the 2 ½ tbsp sugar, stirring until completely dissolved. Add the 4 tbsp soy sauce and bring to the boil. Reduce the heat and simmer for 10 mins, or until the sauce thickens. Turn off the heat and set aside to cool.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Prepare the rice: While the sauce is cooling, start cooking and preparing the rice using your preferred method. We suggest using 200g rice and 260ml water after washing the rice.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Grill the unagi: Preheat your grilling unit to high (about 250°C). Normally eel fillets come sliced in half lengthwise, so cut your 2 eel fillets in half width-wise so they can fit on top of your rice bowl. Line a baking sheet with aluminium foil. Lay the fillets on top and brush with vegetable oil. Place on the grilling unit and grill for 5-7 minutes, or until nicely browned.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Add the unagi sauce: Take the fillets out of the oven and carefully brush with the unagi sauce, leaving a little sauce for later. Place the fillets back on the grilling unit to grill for a further minute or so, until the sauce starts to bubble on top.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Serve and enjoy: To serve, Add a serving of cooked rice to an empty bowl. Brush the top of the rice with the remaining sauce and lay the unagi fillets on top.\n\n"
        "TIPS :\n"
        "- For an authentic experience, you can also service this dish in a two-tier bento lunch box, or jubako. When served like this the dish is called unaju.\n\n"
        "Eel is traditionally eaten during the summer months in Japan. Being rich in vitamins and minerals and protein, the dish is thought to give increased stamina, which is much needed during hot days."

    </string>


    <string name="Pizza_Margherita_Recipe">"Servings: 2"
        "| Cook Time: 1hr 15 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 1,12-inch round of pizza dough, stretched (see NO-2 recipe)\n"
        "- 3 tablespoons tomato sauce \n"
        "- Extra-virgin olive oil\n"
        "- 2¾ounces fresh mozzarella\n"
        "- 4 to 5basil leaves, roughly torn\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Place a pizza stone or tiles on the middle rack of your oven and turn heat to its highest setting. Let it heat for at least an hour.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Put the sauce in the center of the stretched dough and use the back of a spoon to spread it evenly across the surface, stopping approximately ½ inch from the edges.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Drizzle a little olive oil over the pie. Break the cheese into large pieces and place these gently on the sauce. Scatter basil leaves over the top.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Using a pizza peel, pick up the pie and slide it onto the heated stone or tiles in the oven. Bake until the crust is golden brown and the cheese is bubbling, approximately 4 to 8 minutes.\n\n"
        "TIPS :\n"
        "- In a food processor, whiz together whole, drained canned tomatoes, a splash of olive oil and a sprinkle of salt. Keep leftover sauce refrigerated.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Pizza_Dough_Recipe">"Servings: Two 12-inch pizzas"
        "| Cook Time: 20 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 153grams 00 flour (1 cup plus 1 tablespoon)\n"
        "- 153grams all-purpose flour (1 cup plus 1 tablespoon and 2 teaspoons)\n"
        "- 8grams fine sea salt (1 teaspoon)\n"
        "- 2grams active dry yeast (¾ teaspoon)\n"
        "- 4grams extra-virgin olive oil (1 teaspoon)\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- In a large mixing bowl, combine flours and salt.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- In a small mixing bowl, stir together 200 grams (a little less than 1 cup) lukewarm tap water, the yeast and the olive oil, then pour it into flour mixture. Knead with your hands until well combined, approximately 3 minutes, then let the mixture rest for 15 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Knead rested dough for 3 minutes. Cut into 2 equal pieces and shape each into a ball. Place on a heavily floured surface, cover with dampened cloth, and let rest and rise for 3 to 4 hours at room temperature or for 8 to 24 hours in the refrigerator. (If you refrigerate the dough, remove it 30 to 45 minutes before you begin to shape it for pizza.)\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- To make pizza, place each dough ball on a heavily floured surface and use your fingers to stretch it, then your hands to shape it into rounds or squares. Top and bake.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Spaghetti_Carbonara_Recipe">"Servings: 8"
        "| Cook Time: 40 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 1 pound spaghetti\n"
        "- 2 tablespoons olive oil, divided, or as needed\n"
        "- 8 slices bacon, diced\n"
        "- 1 onion, chopped\n"
        "- 1 clove garlic, minced\n"
        "- ¼ cup dry white wine\n"
        "- 4 large eggs, beaten\n"
        "- ½ cup grated Parmesan cheese\n"
        "- salt and black pepper to taste\n"
        "- 2 tablespoons chopped fresh parsley\n"
        "- 2 tablespoons grated Parmesan cheese\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil. Cook spaghetti in boiling water, stirring occasionally, until tender yet firm to the bite, about 12 minutes. Drain, toss spaghetti with 1 tablespoon olive oil, and set aside.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Place diced bacon in a large skillet over medium heat; cook and stir until evenly browned, about 10 minutes. Drain bacon on paper towels, reserving 2 tablespoons bacon fat in the skillet.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Add 1 tablespoon olive oil to bacon fat in the skillet. Add chopped onion and cook over medium heat until onion is translucent. Add minced garlic and cook until fragrant, about 1 minute. Add wine and cook 1 minute more.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Return cooked bacon to the skillet; add cooked spaghetti. Toss to coat and heat through, adding more olive oil if it seems dry or sticks together. Add beaten eggs and cook, tossing constantly with tongs or a large fork, until eggs are barely set. Quickly add 1/2 cup Parmesan cheese and toss again. Season with salt and pepper (remember that bacon and Parmesan are very salty).\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Serve warm with chopped parsley sprinkled on top and extra Parmesan cheese at the table.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Risotto_Recipe">"Servings: 6"
        "| Cook Time: 45 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 6 cups chicken broth, or as needed\n"
        "- 3 tablespoons olive oil, divided\n"
        "- 1 pound portobello mushrooms, thinly sliced\n"
        "- 1 pound white mushrooms, thinly sliced\n"
        "- 2 medium shallots, diced\n"
        "- 1 ½ cups Arborio rice\n"
        "- ½ cup dry white wine\n"
        "- 4 tablespoons butter\n"
        "- 3 tablespoons finely chopped chives\n"
        "- ⅓ cup freshly grated Parmesan cheese\n"
        "- sea salt and freshly ground black pepper to taste\n\n"


        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Gather all ingredients.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Warm broth in a saucepan over low heat.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Meanwhile, warm 2 tablespoons olive oil in a large saucepan over medium-high heat. Add portobello and white mushrooms; cook and stir until soft, about 3 minutes. Remove mushrooms and their liquid to a bowl; set aside.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Add remaining 1 tablespoon olive oil to the saucepan. Stir in shallots and cook for 1 minute. Add rice; cook and stir until rice is coated with oil and pale, golden in color, about 2 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Pour in wine, stirring constantly until wine is fully absorbed. Add 1/2 cup warm broth to the rice, and stir until the broth is absorbed.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "- Continue adding broth, 1/2 cup at a time, stirring constantly, until the liquid is absorbed and the rice is tender, yet firm to the bite, about 15 to 20 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "- Remove from heat. Stir in reserved mushrooms and their liquid, butter, chives, and Parmesan cheese.\n\n"
        "STEP - 08\n"
        "- Season with salt and pepper and serve immediately.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Lasagna_Recipe">"Servings: 12"
        "| Cook Time: 3 hrs 15 mins\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 1 pound sweet Italian sausage\n"
        "- ¾ pound lean ground beef\n"
        "- ½ cup minced onion\n"
        "- 2 cloves garlic, crushed\n"
        "- 1 (28 ounce) can crushed tomatoes\n"
        "- 2 (6.5 ounce) cans canned tomato sauce\n"
        "- 2 (6 ounce) cans tomato paste\n"
        "- ½ cup water\n"
        "- 2 tablespoons white sugar\n"
        "- 4 tablespoons chopped fresh parsley, divided\n"
        "- 1 ½ teaspoons dried basil leaves\n"
        "- 1 ½ teaspoons salt, divided, or to taste\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon Italian seasoning\n"
        "- ½ teaspoon fennel seeds\n"
        "- ¼ teaspoon ground black pepper\n"
        "- 12 lasagna noodles\n"
        "- 16 ounces ricotta cheese\n"
        "- 1 egg\n"
        "- ¾ pound mozzarella cheese, sliced\n"
        "- ¾ cup grated Parmesan cheese\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Gather all your ingredients.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Cook sausage, ground beef, onion, and garlic in a Dutch oven over medium heat until well browned.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Stir in crushed tomatoes, tomato sauce, tomato paste, and water. Season with sugar, 2 tablespoons parsley, basil, 1 teaspoon salt, Italian seasoning, fennel seeds, and pepper. Simmer, covered, for about 1 1/2 hours, stirring occasionally.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil. Cook lasagna noodles in boiling water for 8 to 10 minutes. Drain noodles, and rinse with cold water.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- In a mixing bowl, combine ricotta cheese with egg, remaining 2 tablespoons parsley, and 1/2 teaspoon salt.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "- Preheat the oven to 375 degrees F (190 degrees C).\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "- To assemble, spread 1 1/2 cups of meat sauce in the bottom of a 9x13-inch baking dish. Arrange 6 noodles lengthwise over meat sauce. Spread with 1/2 of the ricotta cheese mixture. Top with 1/3 of the mozzarella cheese slices. Spoon 1 1/2 cups meat sauce over mozzarella, and sprinkle with 1/4 cup Parmesan cheese.\n\n"
        "STEP - 08\n"
        "- Repeat layers, and top with remaining mozzarella and Parmesan cheese. Cover with foil: to prevent sticking, either spray foil with cooking spray or make sure the foil does not touch the cheese.\n\n"
        "STEP - 09\n"
        "- Bake in the preheated oven for 25 minutes. Remove the foil and bake for an additional 25 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 10\n"
        "- Rest lasagna for 15 minutes before serving.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Ravioli_Recipe">"Servings: 4"
        "| Cook Time: 2 hrs\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "Ravioli Dough: \n\n"
        "- 2 cups all-purpose flour\n"
        "- 1 pinch salt\n"
        "- 2 eggs\n"
        "- 1 ½ tablespoons water\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon olive oil\n\n"
        "Ravioli Filling:\n\n"
        "- 1 (8 ounce) container ricotta cheese\n"
        "- 1 (4 ounce) package cream cheese, softened\n"
        "- ½ cup shredded mozzarella cheese\n"
        "- ½ cup shredded provolone cheese\n"
        "- 1 egg\n"
        "- 1 ½ teaspoons dried parsley\n\n"
        "Pesto-Alfredo Cream Sauce: \n\n"
        "- 2 tablespoons olive oil\n"
        "- 2 cloves garlic, crushed\n"
        "- 3 tablespoons prepared basil pesto sauce\n"
        "- 2 cups heavy cream\n"
        "- ¼ cup grated Parmesan cheese\n"
        "- 1 (24 ounce) jar marinara sauce\n\n"
        "Egg Wash: \n\n"
        "- 1 egg\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon water\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Mound flour and salt together on a work surface and form a well. Beat eggs, water, and olive oil in a bowl. Pour 1/2 of the egg mixture into the well. Begin mixing egg and flour with one hand; use your other hand to keep the flour mound steady. Add remaining egg mixture and knead to form a dough.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Knead dough until smooth, 8 to 10 minutes; add more flour if the dough is too sticky. Form dough into a ball and wrap tightly with plastic. Refrigerate for 1 hour.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- While the dough is resting, prepare the ravioli filling: Mix ricotta cheese, cream cheese, mozzarella cheese, provolone cheese, egg, and parsley until well combined. Set the filling aside.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Heat 2 tablespoons of olive oil in a skillet over medium heat. Stir in crushed garlic and pesto sauce and cook for one minute. Stir in heavy cream; increase the heat to high and bring to a boil. Reduce the heat and simmer for 5 minutes. Whisk in Parmesan cheese until melted. Remove the pan from the heat and keep warm.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Meanwhile, warm marinara sauce over medium-low heat in a separate saucepan.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "- Preheat the oven to 375 degrees F (190 degrees C). Beat egg and 1 tablespoon of water together in a small bowl to make the egg wash.\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "- Roll out the pasta dough into thin sheets no thicker than a nickel. To assemble the ravioli, brush the egg wash over a sheet of pasta. Drop cheese filling in 1-teaspoon portions onto the dough, 1-inch apart.\n\n"
        "STEP - 08\n"
        "- Cover the filling with the top sheet of pasta; use your fingers to press around each portion of filling, making the seal as airtight as possible. Cut out individual ravioli with a knife or pizza cutter. Use your fingers to seal the edges.\n\n"
        "STEP - 09\n"
        "- Fill a large pot with lightly salted water and bring to a rolling boil over high heat. Stir in the ravioli and return to a boil. Cook uncovered, stirring occasionally, until the ravioli float to the top and the filling is hot, 4 to 8 minutes. Drain well.\n\n"
        "STEP - 10\n"
        "- Grease a baking sheet. Place the cooked ravioli on the baking sheet and bake in the preheated oven until brown, about 4 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 11\n"
        "- To serve, divide ravioli between four warmed serving bowls. Drizzle marinara sauce on top, followed by cream sauce.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Osso_Buco_Recipe">"Servings: 4"
        "| Cook Time: 1 hr 50 mins\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 2 pounds veal shanks, cut into short lengths\n"
        "- ¼ cup all-purpose flour\n"
        "- ¼ cup Butter\n"
        "- 2 cloves garlic, crushed\n"
        "- 1 large onion, chopped\n"
        "- 1 large carrot, chopped\n"
        "- ⅔ cup dry white wine\n"
        "- ⅔ cup beef stock\n"
        "- 1 (14.5 ounce) can diced tomatoes\n"
        "- salt and pepper to taste\n\n"
        "- Gremolata :\n\n"
        "- ½ cup chopped fresh flat leaf parsley\n"
        "- 1 clove garlic, minced\n"
        "- 2 teaspoons grated lemon zest\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Gather all ingredients.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Dust the veal shanks lightly with flour.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Melt the butter in a large skillet over medium to medium-high heat. Add the veal, and cook until browned on the outside. Remove to a bowl, and keep warm.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Add two cloves of crushed garlic and onion to the skillet; cook and stir until onion is tender.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Return the veal to the pan and mix in the carrot and wine. Simmer for 10 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "- Pour in the tomatoes and beef stock, and season with salt and pepper.\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "- Cover, and simmer over low heat for 1 1/2 hours, basting the veal every 15 minutes or so. The meat should be tender, but not falling off the bone.\n\n"
        "STEP - 08\n"
        "- In a small bowl, mix together the parsley, 1 clove of garlic and lemon zest. Sprinkle the gremolata over the veal just before serving.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Fettuccine_Alfredo_Recipe">"Servings: "
        "| Cook Time: 30 mins\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 24 ounces dry fettuccine pasta\n"
        "- 1 cup butter\n"
        "- ¾ pint heavy cream\n"
        "- salt and pepper to taste\n"
        "- 1 dash garlic salt\n"
        "- ¾ cup grated Romano cheese\n"
        "- ½ cup grated Parmesan cheese\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil. Add fettuccine and cook for 8 to 10 minutes or until al dente; drain.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Melt butter into cream in a large saucepan over low heat; add salt, pepper, and garlic salt. Increase the heat to medium; stir in grated Romano and Parmesan cheese until melted and sauce has thickened.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Add cooked pasta to sauce and toss until thoroughly coated; serve immediately.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Bruschetta_Recipe">"Servings: 8"
        "| Cook Time: 20 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 1 loaf French bread, cut into 1/4-inch slices\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon extra-virgin olive oil\n"
        "- 8 roma (plum) tomatoes, diced\n"
        "- ⅓ cup chopped fresh basil\n"
        "- 1 ounce Parmesan cheese, freshly grated\n"
        "- 2 cloves garlic, minced\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon good quality balsamic vinegar\n"
        "- 2 teaspoons extra-virgin olive oil\n"
        "- ¼ teaspoon kosher salt\n"
        "- ¼ teaspoon freshly ground black pepper\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Gather all ingredients.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Preheat oven to 400 degrees F (200 degrees C).\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Brush bread slices on both sides lightly with 1 tablespoon oil and place on large baking sheet. Toast bread until golden, 5 to 10 minutes, turning halfway through.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Meanwhile, toss together tomatoes, basil, Parmesan cheese, and garlic in a bowl.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Mix in balsamic vinegar, 2 teaspoons olive oil, kosher salt, and pepper.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "- Spoon tomato mixture onto toasted bread slices.\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "- Serve immediately and enjoy!\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Tiramisu_Recipe">"Servings: 12"
        "| Cook Time: 5 hrs 35 mins\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 6 large egg yolks\n"
        "- ¾ cup white sugar\n"
        "- ⅔ cup milk\n"
        "- 1 ¼ cups heavy cream\n"
        "- ½ teaspoon vanilla extract\n"
        "- 1 pound mascarpone cheese, at room temperature\n"
        "- ¼ cup strong brewed coffee, at room temperature\n"
        "- 2 tablespoons rum\n"
        "- 2 (3 ounce) packages ladyfinger cookies\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon unsweetened cocoa powder\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Whisk together egg yolks and sugar in a medium saucepan until well blended.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Whisk in milk and cook over medium heat, stirring constantly, until mixture comes to a boil.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Boil gently for 1 minute, then remove from the heat and allow to cool slightly.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Cover tightly and chill in the refrigerator for 1 hour.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Beat cream and vanilla in a medium bowl with an electric mixer until stiff peaks form.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "- Remove egg yolk mixture from the refrigerator; add mascarpone cheese and whisk until smooth.\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "- Combine coffee and rum in a small bowl. Split ladyfingers in half lengthwise and drizzle with the coffee mixture. Arrange 1/2 of the soaked ladyfingers in the bottom of a 7x11-inch dish.\n\n"
        "STEP - 08\n"
        "- Spread 1/2 of the mascarpone mixture over the ladyfingers, then spread 1/2 of the whipped cream over top. Repeat layers once more.\n\n"
        "STEP - 09\n"
        "- Sprinkle cocoa powder over top.\n\n"
         "STEP - 10\n"
        "- Cover and refrigerate until set, 4 to 6 hours.\n\n"
         "STEP - 11\n"
        "- Enjoy!\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Gnocchi_Recipe">"Servings: 4"
        "| Cook Time: 1 hr\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 2 potatoes, peeled\n"
        "- 2 cups all-purpose flour\n"
        "- 1 egg\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Bring a large pot of salted water to a boil; add potatoes and cook until tender but still firm, about 15 minutes. Drain, cool, and mash with a fork or potato masher.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Combine 1 cup mashed potato, flour, and egg in a large bowl. Knead until dough forms a ball. Shape small portions of the dough into long "snakes". On a floured surface, cut snakes into 1/2-inch pieces.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil. Drop in gnocchi and cook for 3 to 5 minutes or until gnocchi have risen to the top; drain and serve.\n\n"
    </string>


    <string name="Prosciutto_e_Melone_Recipe">"Servings: 4"
        "| Cook Time: 10 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 1 cantaloupe - seeded and cut into 8 wedges\n"
        "- 8 thin slices prosciutto\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Remove the flesh from the rind of the cantaloupe; wrap each piece of cantaloupe with a slice of prosciutto. Arrange on a platter and serve cold.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Panettone_Recipe">"Servings: "
        "| Cook Time: 30 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "For the Panettone dough : \n\n"
        "- 4 tbsp warm milk\n"
        "- 1 tbsp dried yeast\n"
        "- 8 tbsp sugar\n"
        "- 2 sticks butter, room temperature\n"
        "- 5 large eggs, beaten\n"
        "- 2 tsp vanilla extract\n"
        "- grated zest of 1 lemon\n"
        "- grated zest of 1 orange\n"
        "- 3 1/2 cups flour, plus extra (1/2 cup to 2/3 cups more) – see notes below\n"
        "- pinch of salt\n"
        "- 7 tbsp raisins (I like using golden raisins for their beautiful color and flavor)\n"
        "- 3 tbsp rum extract\n"
        "- 8 tbsp candied lemon and orange peel, finely chopped\n"
        "- butter for greasing\n\n"
        "For the topping : \n\n"
        "- egg wash\n"
        "- 1 tbsp icing sugar\n"
        "- more icing sugar for dusting\n\n"
        "Equipment you will need : \n\n"
        "- Panettone cake pan or (Panettone mold) or 8″ deep cake pan\n"
        "- large mixing bowl\n"
        "- silicone brush\n"
        "- large spoon\n"
        "- hand mixer or stand mixer\n"
        "- small saucepan\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "Prepare the yeast :\n\n"
        "- Grease a Panettone pan with softened butter or spray panettone paper molds with baking spray.\n\n"
        "- Place the warm milk in a small bowl and add the yeast and 1 tsp of sugar, mix well and leave for a few minutes.\n\n"
        "- Put the remaining sugar in a large bowl and beat together with the butter and vanilla extract, using a hand mixer, until light and creamy.\n\n"
        "- Add lemon and orange zest and mix.\n\n"
        "- Add the eggs a little at a time until all are well incorporated.\n\n"
        "- If the mixture starts to curdle, add a tablespoon of the flour and beat this in with the eggs.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "Make the dough : \n\n"
        "- Place the flour in a large bowl and mix with a pinch of salt and make a well.\n\n"
        "- Add the yeast mixture (not a sourdough starter) then the butter and egg mixture, folding in with a large spoon to make a soft dough. Alternatively you can use the bowl of a stand mixer and a dough hook set on low speed.\n\n"
        "- Knead for 5 mins in the bowl until the mixture starts to come together and is pretty sticky.\n\n"
        "- Put the dough onto a floured surface and knead for a further 10 mins, until everything has come together and you get a soft, stretchy dough. Add a light sprinkling of flour to the surface and your hands as you go to stop the mixture sticking.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Let the dough rise : \n\n"
        "- Place in a lightly greased bowl and cover with plastic wrap; keep in a warm place for 2 hrs or until doubled in size.\n\n"
        "- Place the raisins in a small saucepan with the rum extract and heat on low for about 5 mins or until the fruit has absorbed the liquid; set aside to cool.\n\n""
        "- When the dough is risen, tip it out onto a lightly floured surface and knead for another 5 mins. Gradually knead in the soaked raisins and chopped candied peel. Shape the dough into a ball and pop into the prepared Panettone pan. If using a 20cm cake pan, wrap a layer of baking parchment around the outside of the tin, to come up about 5cm above the rim, and secure the paper with string. This will help contain the dough as it rises.\n\n"
        "- Cover lightly with plastic wrap and leave to rise for another hour until it has risen to the top of the pan or paper.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n""Bake the cake :\n\n""- Preheat the oven to 350 F.\n\n""- Mix together the icing sugar and egg white and gently brush over the top of the Panettone.\n\n""- Place the Panettone in the oven and bake for 50 – 55 mins or until golden and risen. Insert a skewer into the middle of the cake to test if done before removing from the oven.\n\n""- Leave to cool in the pan for 10 mins before turning out onto a cooling rack.\n\n""- Leave to cool completely before dusting with icing sugar.\n\n""- Cut into wedges to serve.\n\n\n"
        "- This Panettone recipe might be looking fancy and difficult to make but truth is, this is probably one of the easiest desserts you’ll ever make. It might be time consuming to make but in terms of difficulty, this simple Panettone recipe gets all the thumbs up.\n\n"


    </string>

    <string name="Minestrone_Recipe">"Servings: 6 bowls"
        "| Cook Time: 1 hour 5 minutes\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 4 tablespoons extra-virgin olive oil, divided\n"
        "- 1 medium yellow onion, chopped\n"
        "- 2 medium carrots, peeled and chopped\n"
        "- 2 medium ribs celery, chopped\n"
        "- ¼ cup tomato paste\n"
        "- 2 cups chopped seasonal vegetables (potatoes, yellow squash, zucchini, butternut squash, green beans or peas all work)\n"
        "- 4 cloves garlic, pressed or minced\n"
        "- ½ teaspoon dried oregano\n"
        "- ½ teaspoon dried thyme\n"
        "- 1 large can (28 ounces) diced tomatoes, with their liquid (or 2 small 15-ounce cans)\n"
        "- 4 cups (32 ounces) vegetable broth\n"
        "- 2 cups water\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon fine sea salt\n"
        "- 2 bay leaves\n"
        "- Pinch of red pepper flakes\n"
        "- Freshly ground black pepper\n"
        "- 1 cup whole grain orecchiette, elbow or small shell pasta\n"
        "- 1 can (15 ounces) Great Northern beans or cannellini beans, rinsed and drained, or 1 ½ cups cooked beans\n"
        "- 2 cups baby spinach, chopped kale or chopped collard greens\n"
        "- 2 teaspoons lemon juice\n"
        "- Freshly grated Parmesan cheese, for garnishing (optional)\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Warm 3 tablespoons of the olive oil in a large Dutch oven or stockpot over medium heat. Once the oil is shimmering, add the chopped onion, carrot, celery, tomato paste and a pinch of salt. Cook, stirring often, until the vegetables have softened and the onions are turning translucent, about 7 to 10 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Add the seasonal vegetables, garlic, oregano and thyme. Cook until fragrant while stirring frequently, about 2 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Pour in the diced tomatoes and their juices, broth and water. Add the salt, bay leaves and red pepper flakes. Season generously with freshly ground black pepper.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Raise heat to medium-high and bring the mixture to a boil, then partially cover the pot with the lid, leaving about a 1” gap for steam to escape. Reduce heat as necessary to maintain a gentle simmer.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Cook for 15 minutes, then remove the lid and add the pasta, beans and greens. Continue simmering, uncovered, for 20 minutes or until  the pasta is cooked al dente and the greens are tender.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "- Remove the pot from the heat, then remove the bay leaves. Stir in the lemon juice and remaining tablespoon of olive oil. Taste and season with more salt (I usually add about ¼ teaspoon more) and pepper until the flavors really sing. Garnish bowls of soup with grated Parmesan, if you’d like.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Bolognese_Sauce_Recipe">"Servings: 6"
        "| Cook Time: 1 hr 50 mins\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 1 tbsp olive oil\n"
        "- 4 rashers smoked streaky bacon, finely chopped\n"
        "- 2 medium onions, finely chopped\n"
        "- 2 carrots, trimmed and finely chopped\n"
        "- 2 celery sticks, finely chopped\n"
        "- 2 garlic cloves finely chopped\n"
        "- 2-3 sprigs rosemary leaves picked and finely chopped\n"
        "- 500g beef mince\n\n"
        "For the bolognese sauce : \n\n"
        "- 2 x 400g tins plum tomatoes\n"
        "- small pack basil leaves picked, ¾ finely chopped and the rest left whole for garnish\n"
        "- 1 tsp dried oregano\n"
        "- 2 fresh bay leaves\n"
        "- 2 tbsp tomato purée\n"
        "- 1 beef stock cube\n"
        "- 1 red chilli deseeded and finely chopped (optional)\n"
        "- 125ml red wine\n"
        "- 6 cherry tomatoes sliced in half\n\n"
        "To season and serve :  \n\n"
        "- 75g parmesan grated, plus extra to serve\n"
        "- 400g spaghetti\n"
        "- crusty bread to serve (optional)\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Put a large saucepan on a medium heat and add 1 tbsp olive oil.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Add 4 finely chopped bacon rashers and fry for 10 mins until golden and crisp.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Reduce the heat and add the 2 onions, 2 carrots, 2 celery sticks, 2 garlic cloves and the leaves from 2-3 sprigs rosemary, all finely chopped, then fry for 10 mins. Stir the veg often until it softens.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Increase the heat to medium-high, add 500g beef mince and cook stirring for 3-4 mins until the meat is browned all over.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Add 2 tins plum tomatoes, the finely chopped leaves from ¾ small pack basil, 1 tsp dried oregano, 2 bay leaves, 2 tbsp tomato purée, 1 beef stock cube, 1 deseeded and finely chopped red chilli (if using), 125ml red wine and 6 halved cherry tomatoes. Stir with a wooden spoon, breaking up the plum tomatoes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "- Bring to the boil, reduce to a gentle simmer and cover with a lid. Cook for 1 hr 15 mins stirring occasionally, until you have a rich, thick sauce.\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "- Add the 75g grated parmesan, check the seasoning and stir.\n\n"
        "STEP - 08\n"
        "- When the bolognese is nearly finished, cook 400g spaghetti following the pack instructions.\n\n"
        "STEP - 09\n"
        "- Drain the spaghetti and either stir into the bolognese sauce, or serve the sauce on top. Serve with more grated parmesan, the remaining basil leaves and crusty bread, if you like.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Biryani_Recipe">"Servings: 4"
        "| Cook Time: 40 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 300g basmati rice\n"
        "- 25g butter\n"
        "- 1 large onion, finely sliced\n"
        "- 1 bay leaf\n"
        "- 3 cardamom pods\n"
        "- small cinnamon stick\n"
        "- 1 tsp turmeric\n"
        "- 4 skinless chicken breasts, cut into large chunks\n"
        "- 4 tbsp balti curry paste\n"
        "- 85g raisins\n"
        "- 850ml chicken stock\n"
        "- 30g coriander, ½ chopped, ½ leaves picked and 2 tbsp toasted flaked almonds, to serve\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Soak 300g basmati rice in warm water, then wash in cold until the water runs clear.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Heat 25g butter in a saucepan and cook 1 finely sliced large onion with 1 bay leaf, 3 cardamom pods and 1 small cinnamon stick for 10 mins.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Sprinkle in 1 tsp turmeric, then add 4 chicken breasts, cut into large chunks, and 4 tbsp curry paste. Cook until aromatic.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Stir the rice into the pan with 85g raisins, then pour over 850ml chicken stock.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Place a tight-fitting lid on the pan and bring to a hard boil, then lower the heat to a minimum and cook the rice for another 5 mins.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "- Turn off the heat and leave for 10 mins. Stir well, mixing through 15g chopped coriander. To serve, scatter over the leaves of the remaining 15g coriander and 2 tbsp toasted almonds.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Panta_Bhat_Recipe">"Servings: "
        "| Cook Time: 30 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 1 cup basmati rice\n"
        "- salt as required\n"
        "- 2 onion\n"
        "- 3 potato\n"
        "- 1 handfuls coriander leaves\n"
        "- water as required\n"
        "- 3 green chilli\n"
        "- 3 tablespoon mustard oil\n"
        "- 3 red chilli\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- To begin with this easy recipe, soak leftover rice in water and refrigerate it overnight.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Next, to prepare the meal, wash and peel the potatoes and onions. Keep some onions for garnishing.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Next, take a pressure cooker and add water along with potatoes for 2 whistles. Mash the potatoes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Take a pan and add 2 tbsp mustrad oil and allow it to heat, add red chilies along with chopped onions, green chilies, salt, red chili powder along with mashed potatoes. Cook the Aloo Chowkha and add corinader leaves.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Assemble the dish by serving with hot Aloo Chowkha, onions, mustard oil, salt, lemon pieces. Relish the dish and cold and enjoy.\n\n"
        "TIPS :\n"
        "- In case the leftover rice was soaked in excess water, make sure that the excess water is removed and then relished.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Bhuna_Khichuri_Recipe">"Servings: 4"
        "| Cook Time: 1 hr\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "Measurement: 1 cup = 250 ml\n\n"
        "- 2 cups Gobindobhog Chal (Small grain rice)\n"
        "- 1 cup Sona Moong dal (Yellow Split lentils)\n"
        "- 1 large Onion, thin sliced and separated for birista\n"
        "- 1 large Onion, thin sliced\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon Garlic paste\n"
        "- ¾ tablespoon Ginger paste\n"
        "- 1 Tomato, deseeded and diced\n"
        "- 3-4 tablespoons Coriander leaves, chopped\n"
        "- 4 green Chillies\n"
        "- 1 Bay leaf (Tejpatta)\n"
        "- 4 Cardamoms (Elaichi)\n"
        "- 5 Cloves (Laung)\n"
        "- 2 inches Cinnamon stick (Dalchini)\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon Turmeric powder\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon Chilli powder\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon Cumin powder\n"
        "- ½ teaspoon Coriander powder\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon Garam Masala powder\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon Sugar\n"
        "- Salt to taste\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon Ghee (Clarified Butter)\n"
        "- ½ cup Oil for cooking\n"
        "- 6 cups hot Water\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- First take a pan and let it become completely dry. Add the moong dal into the pan and dry roast it over medium flame for 3-4 minutes until the nutty aroma comes up from the dal.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Transfer the dal on a separate utensil and wash the dal once. Then soak the dal in boiled water and cover it. Let the dal soak for an hour and then drain the water. Keep the moong dal aside.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Wash the Gobindobhog chaal 3-4 times until the water gets clear. Then strain the excess water with a strainer and keep it aside to become air dry.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Put a pan on flame and allow it to become completely dry. Then add ½ cup oil into the pan and allow it to become hot.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Once the oil is hot, add thin sliced onion into the pan and fry it over medium flame till crispy golden brown. Then strain the excess oil and transfer the crispy fried onions (Birista) on a separate plate. Keep it aside.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "- Now in the same pan, add whole spices - cinnamon stick, cloves, cardamoms, bay leaves for tempering. Let the spices crackle.\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "- Add sliced onion and fry it over medium flame for 4-5 minutes till soft and translucent.\n\n"
        "STEP - 08\n"
        "- Add garlic paste, ginger paste into the pan and give a nice mix. Cook it over medium flame for another couple of minutes until the raw smell goes away.\n\n"
        "STEP - 09\n"
        "- Add chopped tomatoes and give a nice mix. Close the lid and cook the masala in lowest flame for another 4-5 minutes until the tomatoes become mushy.\n\n"
        "NOTE : Addition of tomatoes make the masala moist and easy to cook.\n\n"
        "STEP - 10\n"
        "- Add 1 teaspoon turmeric powder, 1 teaspoon chilli powder, 1 teaspoon cumin powder, ½ teaspoon coriander powder and give a nice mix.\n\n"
        "STEP - 11\n"
        "- Add 1 tablespoon of water into the pan to cook the masala. Cook the masala over medium low flame until the moisture evaporates and the masala releases oil.\n\n"
        "STEP - 12\n"
        "- Add the gobidobhog rice (Step 3) into the pan and give a nice mix. Cook it over medium flame for 2-3 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 13\n"
        "- Add the soaked moong dal (Step 2) into the pan and give a nice mix.\n\n"
        "STEP - 14\n"
        "- Fry both the rice and dal over medium flame for 6-8 minutes until the rice becomes opaque and a sound comes during the time of stirring. Stir the mixture continuously. This step takes some time to fry the dal-rice properly, but you need to be patient at this point.\n\n"
        "STEP - 15\n"
        "- Add hot water into the pan.\n\n"
        "STEP - 16\n"
        "- Add salt, sugar and give a gentle stir. Cover the pan and cook it over medium flame for 5-6 minutes till the rice becomes visible.\n\n"
        "STEP - 17\n"
        "- Add green chillies, garam masala powder and give a nice stir.\n\n"
        "STEP - 18\n"
        "- Put the flame in lowest and cover the pan. Put a towel over the lid so the steam does not come out of the pan. Cook it for 15 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 19\n"
        "- Take off the lid of the pan and give a gentle stir. Sprinkle birista (Crisy fried onion), chopped coriander leaves, ghee into the pan.\n\n"
        "STEP - 20\n"
        "- Again, close the lid of the pan and seal the pan with towel. Cook it for another 10 minutes in lowest flame. For the perfect textured bhuna khichuri, timing is very important.\n\n"
        "STEP - 21\n"
        "- Switch off the flame and allow the pan to sit for further 15 more minutes. Don’t take off the lid or remove the towel during that time.\n\n"
        "STEP - 22\n"
        "- Take off the towel and lid of the pan after 15 minutes interval and give a gentle mix. Pour the bhuna khichuri into a separate large mixing bowl for fluffy texture, or else it may stick to each other sitting into the hot pan.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Chingri">"Servings: 4"
        "| Cook Time: 30 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 500 Gms Small Prawns\n"
        "- 1 Can coconut milk\n"
        "- 1 medium onion Thinly Chopped\n"
        "- 1 Tsp ginger garlic paste\n"
        "- 5 Tbsp oil\n"
        "- 2 Tbsp butter\n"
        "- 2 Bay leaves\n"
        "- 1 cinnamon stick\n"
        "- 4 cloves\n"
        "- 3 green cardamom\n"
        "- 2-3 Dry Whole Red Chillies\n"
        "- 2 Tsp turmeric powder\n"
        "- 1 Tsp red chilli powder\n"
        "- 2 Tsp Cumin Powder\n"
        "- 2 Tsp Garam masala powder\n"
        "- 1 Tsp Sugar\n"
        "- salt\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Take a bowl and add prawns to it. Add salt and turmeric powder and toss the prawns. Set them aside for a few minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Take a pan and heat oil in it. Sauté the prawns on a medium flame for 5-6 minutes until they turn pink.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- In the same pan, add the chopped onions, bay leaf, dry red chilli, and sauté until the onions turn translucent. Then add the ginger-garlic paste, sugar, cinnamon stick, cloves and cardamom. Sauté for a few minutes. Add salt as required.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Now add the coconut milk to the mixture and let it simmer for 5 minutes on low heat. Then add red chilli powder, turmeric powder and cumin powder.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Add the prawns to the curry. Add garam masala, cover the pan with a lid and let it cook for 4 minutes on medium heat. Garnish with chopped coriander, transfer to a serving bowl and serve hot with steamed rice.\n\n"
        "RECIPE NOTES :\n"
        "- To give the curry a bright colour, you can also add 1 tablespoon of tomato paste.\n\n"
    </string>


    <string name="Fuchka">"Servings: "
        "| Cook Time: 30 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "1 Cup = 250 ml \n\n"
        "For the puri : \n\n"
        "- ½ cup Semolina aka suji\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon all-purpose Flour aka Maida\n"
        "- ¼ teaspoon salt\n"
        "- ⅛ teaspoon or 1 small pinch of Baking soda\n"
        "- 3 tablespoons Water\n"
        "- Oil to deep fry the puris\n\n"
        "For the potato filling : \n\n"
        "- 2 large or 3 medium Potatoes, boiled\n"
        "- 1 small Onion, finely chopped (optional)\n"
        "- 2-3 green Chillies, finely chopped\n"
        "- ¼ cup Coriander leaves, finely chopped\n"
        "- ¼ cup boiled yellow Peas (Matar)\n"
        "- ¼ cup-soaked Kala chana (Black chickpeas)\n"
        "- ¼ cup Tamarind water\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon black Salt\n"
        "- ½ tablespoon Bhaja masala\n"
        "- ½ tablespoon Chaat masala\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon Coriander powder\n"
        "- Salt to taste\n\n"
        "For the phuchka water aka tok jol \n\n"
        "- 30 grams Tamarind\n"
        "- ½ Lime or Gondhoraj lebu\n"
        "- ½ cup of warm Water to soak the tamarind\n"
        "- 2 cups Water, at room temperature\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon Black salt\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon Bhaja masala\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon Chaat masala\n"
        "- ½ teaspoon red Chilli powder\n"
        "- Salt to taste\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "To prepare the puri : \n\n"
        "- Take a mixing bowl and add ½ cup semolina into it.\n"
        "- Add 1 tablespoon all-purpose flour, ¼ teaspoon salt, a small pinch of baking soda into the bowl and mix all the dry ingredients.\n"
        "- Add the required amount of water in small portions slowly into the mixture and mix it nicely to make a soft dough. Knead the dough for 8-10 minutes so that the elasticity forms into the dough. Note:  Make soft dough for the puri. Semolina soaks water and after resting time, it will dry up to perfect consistency.\n"
        "- Cover the dough with a wet kitchen towel and let it rest for half an hour.\n"
        "- After half an hour, knead the dough again for 2 minutes and divide them into equal portions to make large chapati balls.\n"
        "- Put the chapati balls on a roller board. Roll out a thin large chapati with the help of a rolling pin. Cover the other dough ball with a wet cloth during that time.\n"
        "- Cut the chapati into small discs with the help of a cookie cutter or small bowl or lid of any proper-sized container. Cover them with a wet cloth.\n"
        "- Put a pan on flame and allow it to become completely dry. Add oil into a pan for deep frying the puri.\n"
        "- Once the oil is hot, turn the flame to medium-high and slide the puris carefully into the pan and fry them. Once you put the hot oil on the puri, they will puff up. Then flip them with a slotted spoon after puffing up. Tip: Don’t overcrowd the pan. Puris will not get cooked properly if you overcrowd them. Make sure space is there.\n"
        "- Once the puris turn golden, strain the puris from the oil and transfer them to a kitchen tissue-lined plate. The kitchen tissue will absorb the excess oil.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "To prepare the tok jol aka phuchka water : \n\n"
        "- First, soak 30 grams of tamarind in warm water for half an hour. Then mash the pulp with the help of hand.\n"
        "- Strain the pulp with a strainer.\n"
        "- Add ½ lime juice or gondhoraj lebu juice, 2 cups water, salt, 1 teaspoon black salt, ½ teaspoon red chilli powder, 1 teaspoon bhaja masala, and 1 teaspoon chaat masala, one by one into it.\n"
        "- Mix all the ingredients thoroughly and taste. Adjust the amount of salt or spice accordingly. You can leave the lime peels for some extra flavour.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "To prepare the potato filling : \n\n"
        "- Wash potatoes thoroughly and put them in a pressure cooker. Add enough water to pressure cook the potatoes. Close the lid and cook them on medium flame till 2 whistles. Allow the pressure cooker to settle the pressure down. The potatoes must be cooked till firm and not soggy.\n"
        "- Allow the potatoes to cool down completely and then peel off their skin. Take the potatoes into a large mixing bowl and mash them with your hand. Make sure there are no lumps.\n"
        "- Add salt and mix it well.\n"
        "- Add 1 teaspoon black salt, ½ tablespoon bhaja masala, ½ tablespoon chaat masala, 1 teaspoon coriander powder, and ¼ cup tamarind water, one by one into the bowl and mix it well.\n"
        "- Add chopped onion, chopped coriander leaves, green chillies into it and mix them properly.\n"
        "- Add ¼ cup soaked black chickpeas, ¼ cup boiled yellow peas into the bowl and mix them. Make sure the peas don’t get mashed.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "To serve phucka : \n\n"
        "- Make a hole at the centre of each fuchka with the help of your thumb and arrange them on a plate.\n"
        "- Add ½ tablespoon potato filling into the fuchkas.\n"
        "- Dip the whole fuchka in tok jol and fill it in half and serve immediately.\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Bhapa_Recipe">"Servings: 5"
        "| Cook Time: 40 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 2 cups Rice Flour\n"
        "- 1/2 cup Warm Milk\n"
        "- 1/2 tsp Salt\n"
        "- 2 tbsp shredded coconut\n"
        "- 1/2 cup shredded jaggery\n"
        "- Dry rose petals to garnish\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Take the rice flour in a mixing bowl, add in salt and mix them well together. Slowly pour in the milk and mix it well again.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- This mixture will neither be like a dough nor a batter, it will just be wet. Once you take some mixture in your palm, press them to form a ball first and break it down. Keep this mixture aside for 15 mins.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Take a special bhapa pitha pan or a simple momo steamer or anything you can steam with. Add water in the steamer and boil it.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Take a small bowl, and add half of the mixture into the bowl. Then add some coconut and jaggery along with the rest of the mixture.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Now take a wet cotton cloth and close the small bowl, then place it upside down in the steamer. Now remove the bowl slowly and cover the bowl with that cloth. Do not remove the cloth.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "- Cover this pan with a lid and steam it for 5 mins.\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "- Now your dhakai bhapa pitha is ready to be served with a garnish of rose petals.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Ilish_Bhapa_Recipe">"Servings: 4"
        "| Cook Time: 40 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 250 g (or 4 pcs) Ilish machh (hilsa fish, 3-cm-thick pieces)\n"
        "- 40 g Mustard seeds (brown + yellow mixed, soaked for 2 hours)\n"
        "- 8 pcs Green chillies\n"
        "- 40 g Coconut (peeled)\n"
        "- 25 g Yoghurt (beaten)\n"
        "- 22 g Salt\n"
        "- ¼ tsp Sugar\n"
        "- ½ tsp Turmeric powder\n"
        "- 20 g Mustard oil\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Soak mustard seeds in water for 2 hours.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Clean the ilish machh and cut it in 3-cm thick slices. Ilish bhaape is best made with thick slices of fish. Fish without roe (eggs) is fattier and, therefore, ideal for this recipe. If your fish has eggs, remove them, as they may not cook fully when steamed. You can add them to your bhaja (fry) or jhol (curry).\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Drain the mustard seeds of the water they’ve been soaking in and add them to a grinder jar. Add 4 green chillies, roughly chopped, along with the salt and 100g water. Grinding green chillies with the mustard ensures that it doesn’t turn bitter.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Grind these to a fine paste. Take your time with this process. Scrape down the sides of the jar and grind as many times as it takes to form the smoothest possible paste. The finer the grind, the better the flavours.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Now, add the peeled and chopped coconut to the grinder jar. Grind once again until the coconut has broken down completely.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "- Transfer this paste to a steel tiffin box. Add beaten yoghurt, sugar, turmeric, and mustard oil. Mix until the oil is fully incorporated.\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "- Now add the fish, one piece at a time, and coat it with the spices. Use your hands to make sure every part of the fish, including its cavities, is well coated.\n\n"
        "STEP - 08\n"
        "- Slit four more green chillies and place them on the ilish pieces.\n\n"
        "STEP - 09\n"
        "- Fasten the lid of your tiffin box (you could also seal the top with thick aluminium foil) and set the fish aside to marinate for 15 minutes.\n\n"
         "STEP - 10\n"
        "- Heat up your pan and place a stand at the bottom. Pour hot water, making sure it doesn’t reach up to more than half the height of your tiffin box, or there’s a danger of water seeping in. Once the water has come to a boil, place the tiffin on the stand. Cover the pan and steam on medium heat for 15 minutes.\n\n"
         "STEP - 11\n"
        "- Remove from the pan and allow it to rest for another 5 minutes before serving.\n\n"


    </string>


    <string name="Kacchi_Biryani_Recipe">"Servings: 2"
        "| Cook Time: 1hour 50minutes \n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "For crispy fried onions :\n"
        "- 2 to 3 large red onions sliced finely and strands separated\n"
        "- cooking oil to deep fry\n\n"
        "For marination : \n"
        "- 500 grams mutton Raan cut /leg pieces (washed, drained and pat dry completely)\n"
        "- salt to taste\n"
        "- 2 teaspoons caraway seeds shah jeera\n"
        "- 1 a small piece of mace crushed\n"
        "- 3 green cardamom\n"
        "- 1 black cardamom\n"
        "- 2 inch cinnamon stick\n"
        "- 5 cloves\n"
        "- 1 star anise\n"
        "- 1 bay leaf\n"
        "- 1 ½ teaspoon turmeric powder\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon coriander powder\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon red chilli powder\n"
        "- 2 tablespoons ginger garlic paste\n"
        "- 2 to 3 green chillies slit\n"
        "- ½ cup thick yoghurt\n"
        "- handful fresh mint leaves\n"
        "- fistful Fresh coriander leaves\n"
        "- ¾ cup fried onions\n"
        "- ¼ cup oil from the fried onion, preferably\n\n"
        "For par-boiling the rice : \n"
        "- 1½ cups basmati rice washed and soaked in water for 20 to 30 minutes and drained or soak as per packet instructions\n"
        "- 6 cups water\n"
        "- 2 green cardamom\n"
        "- 2 cloves\n"
        "- 2 green chillies slit\n"
        "- 1½ tablespoons fine salt\n\n"
        "Others:\n"
        "- 1 pinch saffron soaked in 2 tablespoons of hot water\n"
        "- fistful fresh mint leaves\n"
        "- ¼ cup fried onions\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon ghee\n"
        "- ¼ cup water reserved after parboiling the rice\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "Prepare the crispy fried onions :\n\n"
        "- Heat enough oil in a wide shallow pan or kadai.\n\n"
        "- Separate the strands of the sliced onions with your hands.\n\n"
        "- Test the oil by dropping one small onion strand, if it sizzles up then you can continue.\n\n"
        "- Drop a handful of onion strands into the hot oil ensuring to spread out and do not overlap.\n\n"
        "- Keep the flame low to medium all time, stir in between to fry evenly and fry till you see the onions changing shades (4 mins).\n\n"
        "- Remove the onions with a slotted spoon on time before they get burnt. The onions will continue to cook even when you take them out, so remove them when you see the golden light brown shade.\n\n"
        "- Spread the fried onions on a paper towel to drain the excess oil (It will become crispy as it cools).\n\n"
        "- Let it cool completely before storing it in an airtight box and in the freezer.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "Marinate the Mutton :\n\n"
        "- Make sure you have washed and drained and pat dried the meat completely so avoid excess moisture.\n\n"
        "- Add the mutton and the rest of the marinade items and mix thoroughly with your hand preferably.\n\n"
        "- Cover and refrigerate overnight or at least 6 hours.\n\n"
        "- Take it out 30 minutes before you start the rice prep.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "Prepare the Rice :\n\n"
        "- Boil the water in a deep large pot with salt, green chillies, cardamoms and cloves.\n\n"
        "- Stir in the drained rice and bring to boil on a high flame.\n\n"
        "- Reduce to medium flame and boil for just about 90 seconds to 2 minutes (30% to 50% cooked) and switch off.\n\n"
        "- Drain the rice in a colander immediately.\n\n"
        "- Reserve ¼ cup of water for later.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "Prepare the Kacchi Mutton Biryani Pot :\n\n"
        "- Spread the marinated mutton in a single layer on the bottom of the biryani pot (oven friendly).\n\n"
        "- Spread the drained rice evenly and pour the reserved water all around (in case you feel the rice is almost cooked because you forgot to drain on time, then skip adding the reserved water).\n\n"
        "- Add the fried onions, mint leaves and saffron water (you may squeeze some lemon juice or rose water and a few dollops of ghee for extra flavour)\n\n"
        "- Cover and seal the pot with foil and then with the lid.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "Bake or Dum cook : \n\n"
        "- If making in the oven, then preheat the oven from 165°C to 170°C with the rack on level 2.\n\n"
        "- If making on a stovetop, place a heat diffuser (or any flat pan) on low flame and keep the biryani pot over the diffuser. This will ensure even heat distribution and prevent the burning of food. Dum-cook for 45 mins to 1 hour. For the oven, keep it up to 1 hour and 10 mins.\n\n"
        "- Open and remove the foil and let it cool for 5 minutes before you stir the rice (You may dig and check if the meat is done. If you feel it needs more cooking, then put it back in the oven. The residue heat of the oven will be enough to get it done)\n\n"
        "- Serve hot with cold salads, kachumber raita, papadams etc.\n\n"
        "Notes : \n"
        "- Crispy fried onions are a must and so should not be skimmed or skipped\n\n"
        "- Make sure the marination is not too runny, so use only thick yoghurt and drain the meat and pat dry before marination\n\n"
        "- Freeze any leftover fried onions in an airtight box for later use\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Pati_Shapta_Recipe">"Servings: 6"
        "| Cook Time: 40 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "For the batter:\n"
        "- 1 cup Refined flour / maida\n"
        "- 1/2 cup Sooji (semolina)\n"
        "- 1/4 cup Rice flour\n"
        "- 1 1/2 - 2 cups Milk\n"
        "- To cook Oil\n\n"
        "For the filling:\n"
        "- 3 cups Coconut / khoya, grated\n"
        "- 2 tbsp Sugar / date jaggery\n"
        "- 3-4 Green cardamoms\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "Prepare the filling:\n\n"
        "- In a wok mix grated coconut or khoya with sugar or jaggery and place it over low flame. If making with khoya, add little milk.\n\n"
        "- Add cardamom in it.\n\n"
        "- Keep stirring the mixture till it gets sticky. Keep aside to cool. The process will take 15-20 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "Prepare the patishapta:\n\n"
        - Take maida, sooji and rice flour in a bowl.\n\n"
        - Add milk. Mix it carefully not making any lumps. Keep the mixture for half an hour.\n\n"
        - Heat the non stick pan. Put a little oil. Pour a thin layer of the mixture on it and spread it quickly with the laddle.\n\n"
        - Put the filling lengthwise at the center of it and roll it. Wait till the colour is light brown.\n\n"
        - Place it on the plate. Serve hot or cold.\n\n"
        - You can pour condensed milk over it before serving.\n\n"


    </string>


    <string name="Mishti_Doi_Recipe">"Servings: 4"
        "| Cook Time: 30 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 1 litre full fat milk or 4 cups milk\n"
        "- 175 to 180 grams palm jaggery or ¾ cup finely chopped palm jaggery\n"
        "- ½ teaspoon cardamom powder\n"
        "- 2 tablespoons Curd or a yogurt starter\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "Boiling Milk :\n\n"
        "- Take 1 litre full fat milk in a heavy kadai or pan. Keep flame to low or medium-low and begin to heat milk.\n\n"
        "- Stir occasionally when the milk is getting heated. Let the milk come to a boil.\n\n"
        "- Then continue to simmer the milk on a low to medium-low flame stirring often.\n\n"
        "- Scrape the dried milk solids from the sides and add to the simmering milk.\n\n"
        "- Simmer milk till it reduces to ⅓ or ½ of its original volume.\n\n"
        "- Keep the kadai down and let the milk cool for about 8 to 9 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "Making Mishti Doi : \n\n"
         "- Meanwhile finely chop or grate 175 to 180 grams palm jaggery. You will need ¾ cup finely chopped palm jaggery.\n\n"
         "- After 8 or 9 minutes, add the chopped palm jaggery. When adding jaggery, the temperature of milk can be 60 to 65 degrees celsius.\n\n"
         "- Mix very well till all the jaggery is dissolved.\n\n"
         "- Add ½ teaspoon cardamom powder. Mix well and let the milk become warm.\n\n"
         "- Check the temperature of milk. It should be warm – meaning if you dip your finger in the milk, your finger should feel comfortably warm but not hot. If you have a cooking thermometer, you can check the temperature. It should be between 40 to 44 degrees celsius.\n\n"
         "- Now add 2 tablespoons curd.\n\n"
         "- With a whisk mix very well. The curd should dissolve in the milk. If you want you can even beat the curd before you add.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "Setting Mishti Doi : \n\n"
        "- Now pour the doi mixture in earthen or terracotta bowls or earthen handi.\n\n"
        "- Cover with a lid or seal with aluminium foil.\n\n"
        "- Keep in a warm place for the mishti doi to set. Mishti doi takes longer to set than curd. the timing will also vary with the temperature in your city. So you can keep for 9 to 24 hours. \n\n"
        "- When it is set, then refrigerate. Serve mishti doi with your meals or as a dessert.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Borhani_Recipe">"Servings: 1"
        "| Cook Time: 10 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- .5 Kilogram Plain Yoghurt\n"
        "- 1/4 teaspoon White pepper powder\n"
        "- 1/2 tablespoon Mustard Powder\n"
        "- 1/2 tablespoon Fresh mint leaves paste\n"
        "- 1/4 teaspoon Red Chili Powder\n"
        "- 1/4 teaspoon Roasted Cumin Powder\n"
        "- 1/4 teaspoon Roasted Coriander Powder\n"
        "- 1/2 teaspoon Ginger Paste\n"
        "- 1/2 teaspoon Green Chili Paste\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon Sugar\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon Black Salt\n"
        "- to taste N/a Salt\n"
        "- 1/2 Cup Water\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Whisk the yogurt well.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- In a blender add mint leaves, coriander leaves, chopped green chili and minced ginger. Puree until smooth.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Then add roasted coriander powder, cumin powder, mustard seeds powder, white pepper powder, sugar and black salt. Blend again by adding whisked yogurt and water. Whizz until frothy.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Keep it refrigerator and let it become cold.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Serve chilled.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Morog_Polao_Recipe">"Servings: 6"
        "| Cook Time: 1 hr 25 mins\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "For the Chicken marinade : \n"
        "- 1.2 kg Chicken legs and thighs - scored with a knife ( bone-in skin off)\n"
        "- ½ cup Greek yoghurt - ~ 150 gm\n"
        "- 1½ tsp Shahi Garam Masala\n"
        "- 2 tbsp Ginger paste - ~ 25 gm Ginger\n"
        "- 1 tbsp Garlic paste - ~ 15 gm Garlic\n"
        "- Salt to taste\n"
        "- 1 tsp Red Chilli powder\n"
        "- 1 tsp Kashmiri red chilli powder\n\n"
        "For cooking Chicken : \n"
        "- 2 tbsp Vegetable oil\n"
        "- 2 tbsp Ghee - or unsalted butter\n"
        "- 6-8 Almonds\n"
        "- 1 large Red Onion - or brown – thinly sliced\n"
        "- 3-4 Cinnamon Bark - ~ 2 inches long\n"
        "- 4 Green Cardamoms\n"
        "- 4 Cloves\n"
        "- 1 Bay leaf - dried\n"
        "- 1 tsp Sugar\n"
        "- Salt to taste\n"
        "- 1 cup Boiling water - or warm water\n"
        "- 1 tsp Kewra or screwpine water\n\n"
        "For the rice Polao/ Pulao :\n"
        "- 2 cups Kalijeera Rice or Gobindobhog Rice - or Gobindobhog rice – Washed and soaked into the water at least for 30 minutes.\n"
        "- 1 large Red Onion - or Yellow Onion\n"
        "- 2-3 Green Cardamoms\n"
        "- 2-3 Cloves\n"
        "- ¼ inch Cinnamon stick\n"
        "- 1 Bay leaf\n"
        "- 2 tbsp Vegetable oil\n"
        "- 2 tbsp Ghee - or unsalted butter\n"
        "- 4 tbsp Whole milk\n"
        "- 15 -20 Raisins\n"
        "- 1 tsp Sugar\n"
        "- 1 tsp Kewra water - or screwpine water ( optional )\n"
        "- 4-6 Green Chillies\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "Marinate The Chicken : \n\n"
        "- Put all the spices under the spice blend section in a spice grinder or coffee grinder and grind them alternating pulsing or whizzing. You will get approximately 1 ½ tsp of the spice blend.\n\n"
        "- Using a sharp knife, score the chicken pieces with 1-inch slits.\n\n"
        "- In a mixing bowl add in yoghurt, red chilli powder, spice blend, ginger and garlic paste, chicken pieces, salt to taste and combine them. Cover with a lid and marinate for 30 minutes on the kitchen counter or overnight in the refrigerator.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "Cook the Chicken ( Morog) : \n\n"
        "- Put in Almonds in a small bowl, pour water and soak the almonds for 30 minutes.\n\n"
        "- Heat oil and Ghee in your dutch oven over medium heat.\n\n"
        "- Reduce the heat to low, add all the whole spices and give a quick stir for a few seconds to release the aroma from the whole spices.\n\n"
        "- Add the sliced onion, sprinkle salt and over medium heat fry the onion until developed golden brown colour. Once done, remove about 2-3 tbsp of fried onion from the dutch oven for garnishing and spread it on a kitchen tissue lined plate.\n\n"
        "- Next, add marinated chicken in the dutch oven and mix with the onion. Increase the heat to high, cook each side for 2 minutes, then flip the other side of the chicken pieces and cook for another 2 minutes on high heat. This way, chicken pieces will develop a golden brown colour and a crispy texture, but also chicken will release some moisture.\n\n"
        "- At this point, add 1 cup of boiling water, give a stir to mix everything well, then over high heat cook for a minute.\n\n"
        "- Once the liquid comes to a rolling boil reduce the heat to medium-low, cover with a lid and cook for 10 minutes, then remove the lid and give a stir so that the inner bottom doesn’t stick. Put the lid back and continue cooking or until the chicken is almost cooked through.\n\n"
        "- Meanwhile, remove the soaked almond skin, put them in a grinder, add a little bit of water to make a paste.\n\n"
        "- Once the chicken is almost cooked, add the almond paste and 1 tsp Kewra water. Mix everything well and over high heat cook for another 3-4 minutes,\n\n"
        "- Don’t wash the Dutch oven, start cooking rice in it.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "Cook Rice ( Polao) : \n\n"
        "- First, drain the soaked rice and place them on a fine sieve.\n\n"
        "- Next, add oil and Ghee in the Dutch oven, wait for a few seconds then add all the whole spices. Stir the spices over medium heat till the aroma released from them.\n\n"
        "- Then add sliced onion, sprinkle salt and fry over medium-high heat till the onion developed a lightly brown colour.\n\n"
        "- Add rice, sprinkle a little bit salt and keep stirring the rice for 3-4 minutes over medium-high heat. Don’t walk away at this point; else you may end up with burnt rice.\n\n"
        "- Now, add 3 ½ cups of boiling water, increase the heat to high and bring to a boil. Cover the cooking pot with a lid, turn off the heat and set the timer for 5 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "Layer the Morog Polao : \n\n"
        "- Uncover the pot, gently remove half of the parboiled or half-cooked rice from the dutch oven to a mixing bowl.\n\n"
        "- Add the cooked chicken and all the gravy in the dutch oven and spread it well.\n\n"
        "- Next, drizzle milk, Kewra water, raisins, sugar.\n\n"
        "- Add the remaining rice, garnish the top with fried onion. Put the lid on and set the dutch oven at the stovetop’s lowest possible setting for 20 minutes.\n\n"
        "- After 20 minutes turn off the heat and wait for another 10 to 15 minutes before serving, serve hot with Bengali garden salad.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Beef_Chui_Jhal_Recipe">"Servings: 5"
        "| Cook Time: 1 hr 55 mins\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 1 kg beef\n"
        "- 250 gm chui jhal\n"
        "- 1 cup onion sliced\n"
        "- 2 tbsp ginger paste\n"
        "- 1 tbsp garlic paste\n"
        "- 1 tbsp cumin paste\n"
        "- 1 tbsp turmeric powder\n"
        "- 1 tbsp red chili powder\n"
        "- 1 tbsp coriander powder\n"
        "- salt to taste\n"
        "- 1/2 tsp nutmeg powder\n"
        "- 1/2 tsp mace powder\n"
        "- 1/2 cup oil\n"
        "- 2-3 pcs bay leaves\n"
        "- 2-1 pcs cinnamon\n"
        "- 3-4 pcs cardamom\n"
        "- 10-12 pcs black pepper\n"
        "- 3-4 pcs cloves\n"
        "- 3-4 pcs dried chilies\n"
        "- 4-5 pcs garlic medium\n"
        "- 3 cups water hot\n"
        "- 1 tsp cumin powder\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Take a stem/twig/root of Chui. Peel the skin.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Cut them into pieces around 1 1/2-inch long. Wash them properly\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Turn off the stove. In a pan take beef (cleaned). The beef pcs should be slightly larger than usual.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Add onion slices, ginger paste, garlic paste, cumin paste, turmeric powder, red chili powder, coriander powder, salt, nutmeg powder, mace powder, oil, bay leaves, cinnamon, cardamom, black pepper, and cloves\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Mix well using the hand. The beef should be mixed with masala very well. The better the mixing, the better the taste. Add water (a little), washing the spices.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "- Close the lid and turn on the stove. Cook for 15 minutes (medium heat). Stir occasionally.\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "- Add dried chilies. Give a stir. Cook for 15 minutes (medium heat). Stir occasionally.\n\n"
        "STEP - 08\n"
        "- When oil separates, add chui pcs. Give a stir.\n\n"
        "STEP - 09\n"
        "- Add whole garlic. Do not cut all the garlic roots. put a layer of the peel on the garlic. Give a stir. Cook for 5 minutes (medium heat).\n\n"
        "STEP - 10\n"
        "- Add 3 cups of hot water. Close the lid. Cook for 40 minutes (medium-low heat). Stir occasionally.\n\n"
        "STEP - 11\n"
        "- Add cumin powder. Give a good mix. Cook for another 10 minutes (low heat).\n\n"
        "STEP - 12\n"
        "- When oil separates, the beef chui jhal is ready to serve.\n\n"
        "STEP - 13\n"
        "- Serve hot!\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Chitol_Maacher_Muitha_Recipe">"Servings: 4"
        "| Cook Time: 1 hr\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- chital macher gada 1 kilogram\n"
        "- cooking oil 200 milli liters\n"
        "- 4 potato (medium size)\n"
        "- 3 tomato (medium size)\n"
        "- 4 onion (medium size)\n"
        "- 3 tablespoon ginger paste mixed with 2-3 green chili (homemade is preferred)\n"
        "- 3 green chili\n"
        "- 3 tablespoon garlic paste\n"
        "- 3 bay leaves\n"
        "- 2 teaspoon cumin paste (cumin seed pasted with little water) or cumin powder\n"
        "- 2 tablespoon ghee\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon garam masala\n"
        "- 3 teaspoon salt\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon turmeric powder\n"
        "- 1 cup water\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "-  Clean the fish and then scoop the fish flesh with a spoon to separate from the bones.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Boil potatoes and peel it. Then mash the potatoes a paste.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "-  Cut the onions and tomatoes into small pieces. Keep the other ingredients aside.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Mix the mashed potato, fish (flesh),ginger-green chili paste(1 Â½ table spoon), garlic paste (3 table spoon), onion cuts (2 big) and salt (1 tea spoon)\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "-  Heat oil in a kadhai or pan. Add small hand made balls (pakora shape) of the mix to the heated oil and deep fry\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "- After all the mix is fried, add the bay leaves , remaining onion ( 2) to the left over oil and fry for 2 minutes. After 3-4 minutes add cut tomato cuts and stir for another 3-4 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "- Add ginger- green chili paste (1 Â½ table spoon), turmeric powder and cumin paste (2 table spoon), mix it well and allow it to cook for 3-4 minutes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 08\n"
        "- Add 1 cup of water, and allow it to boil. Add the remaining salt (2 tea spoon). Bring it to boil.\n\n"
        "STEP - 09\n"
        "- Add fried fish pakoras and sliced green chili ( 2 medium) and allow to boil for 5 minutes. After that, add ghee ( 2 tea spoon) and garam masala powder (1 tea spoon). Add salt to taste and mix it well. Ready to be served with white rice.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Shami_Kebab_Recipe">"Servings: 4"
        "| Cook Time: 50 min\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "1 CUP = 240ML \n\n"
        "- 350 to 400 grams chicken boneless (if using chicken with bone, refer notes)\n"
        "- ⅓ cup chana dal or 75 grams, 1 cup soaked\n"
        "- 1 tsp red chili powder\n"
        "- ¼ tsp turmeric\n"
        "- 1 inch cinnamon stick/dalchini\n"
        "- 2 to 3 cardamoms / elaichi\n"
        "- 1 to 2 red chilies\n"
        "- 1 inch gingerchopped\n"
        "- 3 garlic cloves large , chopped\n"
        "- 1 tsp cumin / jeera\n"
        "- 1 tsp garam masala \n"
        "- Water as needed (I used about half cup)\n"
        "- Salt as needed\n"
        "- 1 onion small , finely chopped\n"
        "- 2 eggs – 1 for the mixture – 1 for coating\n"
        "- 1 Handful coriander leaves\n"
        "- 1 Handful mint leaves / pudina leaves\n"
        "- 1 green chili\n"
        "- Oil as needed\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Wash and soak chana dal for about 2 to 4 hours. Well soaked dal provides a good texture to the kababs. Drain it and add to a large pot.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Add ginger, garlic, salt, turmeric, red chili powder, whole red chilies, garam masala, cinnamon stick, jeera, green cardamoms and chicken. Add water to partially cover the chicken. Do not add too much water\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "- Cook all these partially covering the pot until chicken and dal are soft cooked\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "- Evaporate water completely. This step is very important otherwise the kebab mixture will turn mushy and will not hold shape.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "- Cool this completely and remove the whole spices and any bones if used chicken on bone.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "How to Make Shami Kabab :\n\n"
        "- Add this to a processor or a blender and make a coarse mixture.\n\n"
        "- The mixture should turn fairly dry and powdery\n\n"
        "- Add green chilies, onions, pudina, coriander leaves. Mix and check the salt and spice. If needed add more.\n\n"
        "- Break an egg to a bowl and beat it lightly to mix the yolk and the white uniformly. \n\n"
        "- Add this little by little to the mixture and form a dough. Do not pour the egg at one time, do it in parts add use only as needed for binding. You can also squeeze this mixture a bit for the moisture to release. Then add the egg only as needed\n\n"
        "- Divide the dough to 8 to 10 equal parts and make balls. Flatten them and make kebabs on your palm. Place them on a plate\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "Frying :\n\n"
        "- Heat oil for shallow frying in a wide pan. I fried all the kababs in 2 batches\n\n"
        "- Break an egg to a bowl and beat it lightly just to mix the yolk and white uniformly\n\n"
        "- When the oil turns hot enough, dip one kebab each time in the egg and lift it with a fork.\n\n"
        "- Gently shake off the excess egg to avoid the oil turning messy\n\n"
        "- Drop these in the hot oil. Fry on a medium heat until golden, flipping to and fro.\n\n"
        "- When they are golden fried, transfer them to a plate with kitchen tissues.\n\n"
        "- Serve chicken shami kabab hot with mint chutney\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Paneer_Tikka_Recipe">"Servings: 4"
        "| Cook Time: 2 hrs 30 mins\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        "- 266.67 to 333.33 grams Paneer or Indian cottage cheese\n"
        "- 0.67 cup diced onions or 1 medium sized onion\n"
        "- 0.67 diced capsicum or 1 small to medium bell pepper – green, yellow or red\n\n"
        "For Paneer Tikka Marination : \n"
        "- 266.67 grams Hung Curd or greek yogurt\n"
        "- 1.33 tablespoon Ginger Garlic Paste or 1 tablespoon crushed ginger-garlic\n"
        "- 2.67 teaspoons kashmiri red chili powder or 2 teaspoons sweet paprika\n"
        "- 0.67 teaspoon turmeric powder (ground turmeric)\n"
        "- 1.33 teaspoon cumin powder (ground cumin)\n"
        "- 1.33 teaspoon Coriander Powder (ground coriander)\n"
        "- 0.67 teaspoon Garam Masala\n"
        "- 1.33 teaspoon ajwain (carom seeds)\n"
        "- 1.33 teaspoon dry mango powder (amchur powder)\n"
        "- 1.33 teaspoon chaat masala\n"
        "- 0.67 teaspoon black pepper powder – optional (ground black pepper)\n"
        "- 2 teaspoons lemon juice\n"
        "- 1.33 tablespoon mustard oil or any neutral tasting oil\n"
        "- 0.67 teaspoon black salt – optional\n"
        "- salt as required\n"
        "- some mustard oil for brushing\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Chop the paneer in square shaped cubes.\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Dice the onions and capsicum in 1 or 1.5 inches square pieces.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "Making Marination : \n\n"
        "- In a large bowl, take the hung curd (greek yogurt) and whisk it lightly till it becomes smooth\n\n"
        "- Add ginger-garlic paste, all the spice powders, carom seeds, black salt, regular salt, lemon juice and mustard oil.\n\n"
        "- Mix very well. Check the taste and add more seasonings if required.\n\n"
        "- Add the veggies and paneer to the marinade. Slowly and gently mix them with the marinade.\n\n"
        "- Cover the bowl and marinate for at least 2 hours or more in the refrigerator.\n\n"
        "- After 2 hours thread the paneer and veggies alternately on bamboo skewers. Soak or rinse the bamboo skewers before threading. \n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "Grilling Paneer Tikka :\n\n"
        "- Preheat the oven for 15 to 20 minutes at 230 or 240 degree celsius or 464 degrees Fahrenheit. Use only the top heating element. \n\n"
        "- Line a baking tray with aluminium foil or parchment paper. Arrange the paneer skewers on the tray. Brush some oil on the veggies and paneer cubes all over.\n\n"
        "- Place the tray on the top rack. Grill the paneer tikka first for 7 to 10 minutes at 230 or 240 degree celsius or 464 degrees Fahrenheit. Then remove and turn the skewers.\n\n"
        "- Place back on the top rack in the oven and continue to grill for 3 to 5 minutes more till the edges of the paneer are golden or slightly charred. Do not grill for a long time as then paneer cubes becomes hard. \n\n"
        "- Since temperatures vary from oven to oven do keep a check. You can reduce or increase the time as required. Total grilling time will be 15 to 20 minutes.\n\n"
        "- Remove from the oven and then place the paneer cubes on a serving plate. Sprinkle some chaat masala and lemon juice.\n\n"
        "- Serve paneer tikka with mint chutney and onion rings with lemon wedges\n\n"
        "NOTES :\n"
        "- Barbecue: You can even use the barbecue grill for making the paneer tikka.\n\n"
        "- Grilling in the oven: In the oven grill for 15 to 20 minutes at 230 or 240 degree celsius with only the top heating element on.\n\n"
        "- Marination Time: I always suggest to marinate the paneer cubes for 2 hours or more. You can also keep the marinated paneer overnight in the fridge. More marination, the better the flavors get infused in the paneer and veggies.\n\n"
        "- Vegetables: Add a mix of veggies like bell pepper, onions, tomatoes, baby corn, mushrooms, cauliflower, tomatoes, broccoli etc. For cauliflower blanch them before marinating. \n\n"
        "- Adding Oil: While grilling the paneer cubes and veggies can become dry. Hence oil is added to the marination mixture. The paneer cubes and veggies are also brushed with some oil to avoid them from becoming dry.\n\n"
        "- Overcooking: Don’t overcook the paneer as they then become rubbery, dry and hard. The paneer should be soft, well cooked and yet succulent.\n\n"
        "- Marinade: The extra marinade can be applied or brushed on the paneer tikka before grilling them. If you are making paneer tikka masala gravy, you can use the extra marinade in the gravy.\n\n"
        "- Vegan Options: Use tofu, seitan or tempeh in place of paneer. Use a vegan yogurt like almond or cashew yogurt in place of dairy yogurt.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Samosa">"Servings: 10 Somosa "
        "| Cook Time: 55 mins\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        " 1 cup = 240 ml \n\n"
        "For Samosa Dough :\n"
        "- 2 cups all-purpose flour (organic maida) (250 grams )\n"
        "- ¼ cup oil or melted ghee (60 ml)\n"
        "- 6 tablespoons water (¼ cup + 2 tbsp )\n"
        "- ¾ teaspoon carom seeds (ajwain)\n"
        "- ¾ teaspoon salt\n\n"
        "For potato filling :\n"
        "- 4 potatoe (500 grams)\n"
        "- ½ cup green peas (boiled or frozen)\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon oil or ghee\n"
        "- 1 tablespoon ginger minced or paste\n"
        "- 1 to 2 green chilies chopped (optional)\n"
        "- 1 pinch hing (asafoetida) (optional)\n"
        "- 4 tablespoons coriander leaves chopped finely\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon lemon juice (or ½ tsp amchur or chaat masala)\n"
        "- ½ teaspoon salt (adjust to taste)\n\n"
        "Spices :\n"
        "- ¾ teaspoon cumin seeds\n"
        "- ¾ to 1 teaspoon garam masala \n"
        "- ¾ teaspoon red chilli powder (adjust to taste)\n"
        "- ½ teaspoon cumin powder\n"
        "- ½ teaspoon fennel powder (optional)\n\n"

        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- HOW TO MAKE THE RECIPE :\n\n"
        -  Boil potatoes just until done without making mushy. You can either boil them in a steamer, pot or a cooker. (refer notes)\n\n"
        - Crumble them, do not mash them up. Set aside\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "Make Samosa Dough (or use frozen puff pastry sheets) :\n\n"
        "- Mix together flour, carom seeds, salt and oil in a mixing bowl.\n\n"
        "- Rub the flour well for 2 to 3 mins in between the palms to incorporate the oil or ghee well\n\n"
        "- Take handful of flour and press down with your fingers. It must hold shape and not crumble.\n\n"
        "- Add water little by little and mix the flour to form a stiff dough. It should be stiff and not soft dough. Cover and rest for 25 to 30 mins.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "Make Potato Filling :\n\n"
        "-  Heat a pan with oil. Add cumin seeds.\n\n"
        "- When they begins to sizzle, add ginger and green chilies. Fry until ginger smells good, for about 30 to 60 seconds.\n\n"
        "- Next add green peas and saute for 2 mins. \n\n"
        "- Add red chilli powder, garam masala, cumin powder, chaat masala (optional) and fennel powder. Saute for 30 seconds.\n\n"
        "- Next add potatoes and sprinkle salt. Mix and saute for 2 to 3 mins. Mix in coriander leaves and set aside to cool\n\n"
        "- Taste and add more salt if needed. If using lemon juice, add it now.\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "How to Make Samosa : \n\n"
        "- Knead the dough gently to smoothen a bit. Make 5 portions and roll to balls. Cover the dough.\n\n"
        "- Grease the rolling area and then flatten a ball. Drizzle some oil.\n\n"
        "- Begin to roll to oval shape of 8.5 inches long by 6.5 inches wide. It should be neither too thick or too thin. (watch video)\n\n"
        "- Cut it to two parts. The 2 parts make 2 samosas. If the edges are too thick, gently roll it to thin down.\n\n""
        "- Take one part and apply water over the straight edge (towards the cut side). Join the edges to make a cone. Press down gently to seal the cone from inside as well. (check video or step by step photos above)\n\n"
        "- Fill the cone with potato masala and press down with your finger to push it inside the cone. Smear water generously on both the other edges\n\n"
        "- Bring the edges together and seal them by pinching off the edges together. If you prefer to make a standing samosa, make a pleat on one side. Bring back the pleat and seal it by pinching off the edges together. (check video or step by step photos above)\n\n"
        "-  Make sure the samosa has been sealed well. (check photos or video). Cover them witha cloth to prevent drying.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "Deep Fry :\n\n"
        "- After you make 5 samosas, begin to heat the oil until medium hot\n\n"
        "- Oil has to be medium hot and not very hot. A piece of dough dropped in the oil should not sizzle or rise immediately. Instead you should see tiny bubbles in the oil and the dough should take a while to come up to the surface. This is the right temperature\n\n"
        "- Gently add as many samosas as you can to the oil and fry them on a low flame undisturbed for few minutes (about 10 to 12 mins).\n\n"
        "- When the crust becomes firm, increase the flame to medium. Rotate them to the other side and fry until crispy and golden.\n\n"
        "- While the first batch of samosas fry, make the rest of them.\n\n"
        "- Remove the golden fried ones on to a colander. Let the temperature of oil come down slightly before you fry the next batch.\n\n"
        "- Serve samosa with mint chutney sweet tamarind chutney or tomato sauce. \n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "Bake Samosa in Oven : \n\n"
        "-  Preheat the oven at 180 C or 360 F for about 20 mins. Brush each samosa generously with oil all over and place them on a prepared tray. Bake these for about 35 to 40 mins\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "In the Air Fryer : \n\n"
        "- Spray your samosa with oil or brush with ghee. Preheat your air fryer for 7 mins at 360 F or 180 C if required.\n\n"
        "- Place the samosa in the air fryer basket or tray spacing them at least an inch apart from each other.\n\n"
        "- Air fry for 12 mins, turn them to the other side and air fry for another 5 to 6 mins, or a little longer until golden and crisp. (In non-preheated air fryer air fry at 370 F or 190 C for the same time)\n\n"
        "- Brush them with ghee or oil as required.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Butter_Chicken_Recipe">"Servings: 4"
        "| Cook Time: 45 mins\n\n"
        "INGREDIENTS : \n\n"
        " 1 CUP = 240ML\n\n"
        "- ½ kg (1.1 lbs) boneless chicken (read notes)\n"
        "- ½ to ¾ teaspoon Kashmiri red chili powder (or paprika adjust to taste, reduce for kids) \n"
        "- ¼ to ⅓ teaspoon salt (adjust to taste)\n"
        "- ¾ to 1 tablespoon lemon juice\n\n"
        "Second Marination :  \n"
        "- ⅓ cup Greek yogurt (hung curd/thick curd, refer notes)\n"
        "- ¾ tablespoon ginger garlic paste\n"
        "- ⅛ teaspoon turmeric (haldi)\n"
        "- ¾ to 1 teaspoon garam masala (adjust to taste)\n"
        "- ½ teaspoon cumin powder (optional)\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon coriander powder (optional)\n"
        "- 1 teaspoon kasuri methi (optional, dried fenugreek leaves)\n"
        "- ¾ to 1 tablespoon oil\n\n"
        "For sauce : \n"
        "- 2 to 3 tablespoons butter or ghee (divided)\n"
        "- 2 inch cinnamon piece\n"
        "- 2 to 4 green cardamoms \n"
        "- 2 to 4 cloves\n"
        "- 3 cups (600 grams, 24 oz) fresh tomato puree (1x - 4 large tomatoes) \n"
        "- ¾ tablespoon ginger garlic paste \n"
        "- 1 to 2 green chilies (deseed, slit or chop, optional)\n"
        "- 20 to 22 cashews (or almond flour, read notes) \n"
        "- ½ cup water to blend cashews or almond flour \n"
        "- 1 to 2 teaspoons Kashmiri chili powder (reduce for kids, adjust to taste)\n"
        "- 1 to 1½ teaspoons garam masala (divided, adjust to taste) \n"
        "- 1 to 1½ teaspoon coriander powder (optional, adjust to taste) \n"
        "- ½ teaspoon cumin powder (optional, adjust to taste) \n"
        "- ½ to ¾ teaspoon salt (adjust to taste) \n"
        "- 1 teaspoon sugar (to balance the flavors)\n"
        "- ½ tablespoon Kasuri methi (dried fenugreek leaves) \n"
        "- 1½ cups hot water \n"
        "- ⅓ cup (80 to 100 ml) heavy cream or whipping cream (divided)\n"
        "- 2 tablespoons coriander leaves (fine chopped to garnish)\n\n"




        "--------------------------\n\n"

        "DIRECTIONS : \n\n"
        "STEP - 01\n"
        "- Add chicken to a large mixing bowl and pat dry if required to get rid of
any excess moisture. Add lemon juice, chili powder and salt. Mix well to
marinate. Cover and rest for 20 minutes.
\n\n"
        "STEP - 02\n"
        "- Next add yogurt, kasuri methi, oil, turmeric, ginger garlic paste, coriander
powder, cumin powder and garam masala powder. Mix well.\n\n"
        "STEP - 03\n"
        "-  Cover and rest in the refrigerator for at least 12 hours. You can keep it as
long as 48 hours. Longer resting time results in tender and juicy chicken.
\n\n"
        "STEP - 04\n"
        "To make tomato and cashew puree: \n\n"
        "- Option 1 - If you have a powerful blender, you can blend the cashews
and tomatoes together until smooth. If you want you can also soak the
cashews in hot water for 30 mins and then use here.\n\n"
        "- Option 2 – Puree the tomatoes in a large blender and cashews in a small
grinder with half cup water, added in 2 batches.
\n\n"
        "- You need smooth puree of both. Set these aside.\n\n"
        "STEP - 05\n"
        "Make the sauce : \n\n"
        "- When you are ready to make the butter chicken, place the chicken out of
the refrigerator at this point as we don’t want to cook very cold chicken\n\n"
        "- Heat a pan with butter and add all the whole spices - cinnamon, cloves and
cardamoms.
\n\n"
        "- Let them sizzle for a minute. Add ginger garlic paste and green chilies. Fry
on a low heat, for a minute or 2, till it turns fragrant but not burnt.\n\n"
        "- Turn off the heat and stir in red chili powder, garam masala, cumin and
coriander powder.\n\n"
        "- Place a strainer over the pot and pour the pureed tomatoes (or tomato
cashew puree if made separately). Use a sturdy spoon to help pass the
puree.
\n\n"
        "- Mix well and cover partially. Bring it to a boil on a medium high heat.
Later reduce the heat to low or medium and cook partially covered until the tomato puree turns thick. Keep stirring in between. This step takes
about 15 minutes without cashews included. With cashews it takes
lesser time.
\n\n"
        "- When you see the tomato puree is thick, stir in the Cashew puree. Pour
hot water and mix.\n\n"
        "- Simmer this partially covered for 10 mins, until the sauce thickens and
traces of fats/butter are visible on top of the sauce.\n\n"
        "STEP - 06\n"
        "- Grill or roast chicken in an oven or stovetop :\n\n"
         "- While the sauce simmers, roast/ bake or grill the chicken in the oven or
stovetop.\n\n"
         "- Option 1 - In the oven: Preheat the oven to 240 C or 460 F for at least
15 minutes. Skew the chicken on to soaked wooden skewers or place on
a greased tray and bake for 20 to 22 minutes, depending on the size of
chicken pieces. In between you will have to turn to the other side.
Chicken should be tender and not overcooked.
\n\n"
         "- Option 2 - On the stovetop, spread one tbsp. butter or ghee in a
griddle/pan and heat it well. Place the marinated chicken pieces, spacing
them a little apart\n\n"
         "- Fry on a medium heat for 2 mins. Ignore the moisture oozing out of the
chicken. Turn the chicken pieces to the other side, don’t burn and do not
overcook.\n\n"
         "-  Cook till the chicken is just done and all the marinade dries up. This way
roast the chicken pieces in 2 to 3 batches, depending on the size of your
skillet. It is not necessary to fully cook the chicken at this stage.\n\n"
         "- Optional - If you want browned chicken, increase the flame to high and
roast until they turn golden or light brown on both the sides. Be careful
as this can easily burn the masala and overcook the chicken.\n\n"
        "STEP - 07\n"
        "How to make Butter Chicken :\n\n"
         "- Add chicken to the butter chicken gravy. Pour more hot water (about ½
cup) if the sauce is too thick. Cover and simmer for about 5 to 7 minutes
till it becomes tender. This additional water is not mentioned in the recipe
and is optional depending on how long you cook.
\n\n"
         "- Stir in salt, sugar and kasuri methi. Taste test and optionally add more
garam masala and another tablespoon butter for additional flavour (both
are optional).\n\n"
         "- Stir in heavy cream. Or Take a few tablespoons of the hot gravy to a
small bowl and stir in the cream to temper it first. Mix that with the rest of
the sauce.
\n\n"
         "- Garnish Butter Chicken with chopped coriander leaves and some cream.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="Rogan_Josh_Recipe">
    </string>


</resources>